Keep the tape going until it's built all the way to the starting point by
テープが開始点まで構築されるまでテープを続けます。
finish thebarsr that had been formatted before.
以前にフォーマットしたbarsrを終了します。
Then dig some more, and build in some really nice things that are ready earned.
次に、さらに掘り下げて、すぐに手に入る本当に素晴らしいものをいくつか組み込みます。
Those float doors will create some similar architecture to this little corner.
これらのフロートドアは、この小さなコーナーに似たような建築物を作り出すでしょう。
I used to work on p Putin's writers by six hundred when the lights lights went out.
私は照明が消える600時までにプーチン大統領の作家の仕事をしていました。
Now the talent activated will help the comments that more people were buying,
アクティブ化されたタレントは、より多くの人が購入していたコメントを支援します。
Now Āijhāmāsāka must be built in WWanjatana
今、ĀijhāmāsākaはWWanjatanaに建てられなければなりません
Āijhāmāsaka should be created in WWanjatana
Āijhāmāsaka は WWanjatana で作成する必要があります
Good evening, gentlemen, hello, everyone
こんばんは、紳士諸君、こんにちは、皆さん
It's great to have so many people listening to us today
今日はたくさんの人に聞いてもらえてとてもうれしいです
A speech by Hong Sang-sung, a specific researcher
ホン・サンソン特定研究者の講演
First let me briefly introduce his background
まずは彼の経歴を簡単にご紹介します
Shang Chenghe is actually from Qigu Township, Tainan County
尚承和さんは、実は台南県七股郷の出身です。
A child who grew up in the countryside
田舎で育った子供
But he didn't study well
しかし彼はよく勉強しませんでした
He later entered the Chemistry Department of Qingda University
その後、青達大学化学科に入学
After 1 month at a very young age
非常に若い年齢で1か月後
Received a Ph.D. from Qingda University before the age of 30
30歳前に青達大学で博士号を取得
very impressive
非常に印象的
He is Professor Liao Juncheng of Qingda University
彼は青達大学の廖俊成教授です。
Also a beneficiary student of Professor Guan Bijun
そしてグアン・ビジュン教授の恩恵を受けた学生たち
After he got his Ph.D.
彼が博士号を取得した後、
Received the Ministry of Education's postdoctoral study abroad scholarship
文部科学省博士研究員海外留学奨学金を受給
Sweeps and Pengshui in the United States, our Zhongnanjun Institute
米国の掃除と澎水、私たち中南軍研究所
The current President of the Hong Kong Council
現在の香港評議会議長
Three years of postdoctoral research
3年間のポスドク研究
Then when he comes back
それから彼が戻ってきたら
Consistently excellent research performance
一貫して優れた研究業績
upper he actually
上の彼は実際に
The main focus of his research
彼の研究の主な焦点
It is in the part of Tang Chemistry and Tang Biology
それは唐の化学と唐の生物学の一部です
Then he is in these special
それから彼はこれらの特別な中にいます
on the cell membrane
細胞膜の上に
The analysis of these bullets
これらの弾丸の分析
quite accomplished
かなり完成度が高い
We published his reading in
私たちは彼の朗読を以下に出版しました
our people in science
私たちの科学分野の人々
If there is an article published in a natural journal
自然誌に掲載された論文がある場合
that's a shame
残念です
that upper he has this one
あのアッパー、彼はこれを持っています
Nature
自然
And Nature Chemistry
そして自然化学
is Nature Journal
ネイチャージャーナルです
Journal of Natural Chemistry
自然化学ジャーナル
and the Journal of the American Chemical Society
および米国化学会誌
This very important chanting
このとても大切な唱えは、
Of course his research is very good
もちろん彼の研究は非常に優れています
Of course it's the winning document
もちろん、それは勝利の文書です
The public health label I just told him about
先ほど彼に話した公衆衛生ラベルについて
he got this congressional
彼はこれを議会で受け取った
Academic Awards of the Ministry of Education
文部科学省学術賞
And our former dean
そして私たちの元学部長
Brilliant talent machine driven
優秀な才能を機械が駆動する
Distinguished Talent Award
優秀な才能賞
And won the TECO Award
そしてTECO賞を受賞
There is also the Contribution Award for Li Tiande's medical achievements
李天徳氏の医学的業績に対する貢献賞もある
So in terms of research
研究という観点から言えば
The upper level is quite outstanding
上のレベルはかなり優秀です
he got it very young
彼はとても若くしてそれを理解した
This is the chairperson of the Congress
こちらは議会の議長です
Zhu Jingyi's words
朱静儀の言葉
It is said that the medals filled with film on the body are like this
体にフィルムが詰まったメダルはこんな感じだそうです
but one important thing
でも一つ重要なこと
In addition to doing a good job in his research
研究で良い仕事をすることに加えて、
He is also enthusiastic about teaching
指導にも熱心です
He interacts well with students
彼は生徒たちとよく交流している
So he got Tsinghua University
それで彼は清華大学に合格した
this outstanding teacher
この優秀な先生
quite difficult
かなり難しい
So we specially invite him to give a speech to you today.
そこで、今日は特別に彼にスピーチをしてもらうことにしました。
because he is a good speaker
彼は話が上手なので
He will introduce to you today
今日は彼があなたに紹介します
This parishioner
この氏子
he will tell everyone
彼はみんなに言うでしょう
This hall of wisdom
この知恵の殿堂
With you Zhitang's Tang
あなたと一緒に Zhitang の唐
why is it different
なぜ違うのですか
Then tell everyone what is called
それからみんなに何と呼ばれているか教えてください
Bangtang Shuangtang Guatang Genduotang
バンタン シュアンタン グアタン ゲンドゥオタン
In this part, we often hear some
この部分でよく聞かれるのが、
related health food and some
健康食品関連など
Some proteins related to sugar, etc.
糖質などに関係する一部のタンパク質
It is very specialized in this research on the structure of sugar
砂糖の構造に関するこの研究は非常に専門的です
and it also participates in the
にも参加しています
These analyzes of the structure of this glycoprotein
この糖タンパク質の構造を解析した結果
and the analysis of the functions of these proteins in relation to sugars and sugars
および糖と糖に関連したこれらのタンパク質の機能の分析
Recently in our genome center
最近私たちのゲノムセンターで
We are under the leadership of the University's Dean Au
私たちは大学のオー学部長のリーダーシップの下にあります。
We started to make sugar-based vaccines against cancer
私たちは砂糖をベースにしたガンに対するワクチンの製造を開始しました
Everyone has said that vaccines are used to prevent infectious diseases
ワクチンは感染症を防ぐために使用されると誰もが言っています。
But we can now use this sugar-based
しかし、今ではこの砂糖ベースのものが使えるようになりました。
to target such a vaccine to treat cancer
がんの治療を目的としたワクチンの開発
this is something new
これは何か新しいことです
So you don't need to come here today
だから今日はここに来る必要はないよ
Can get a lot of scientific knowledge
多くの科学的知識を得ることができる
But the upper layer, apart from being a good scientist
しかし、上層部は、優れた科学者であることは別として、
It's also usually a good scientist
普段は優秀な科学者でもある
After a very high level
非常に高いレベルを経て
Science and art can probably be combined
科学と芸術はおそらく組み合わせることができる
So he ended up telling us
それで彼は結局私たちにこう言いました
What kind of connection does Tanggen axion have?
タンゲンアクシオンとはどのような関係があるのでしょうか？
really delicate thing
本当にデリケートなこと
So we are very happy to have such a rich theme today
今日はこのような内容の濃いテーマができてとても嬉しいです
You can come and listen to the introduction given by the upper level
上級者による紹介を聞きに来てください。
We'll have 30 minutes of Q&A later
この後30分間質疑応答を行います
So guys we're going to let the red-specific researcher
それで、赤に特化した研究者に任せましょう
finish all first
まずすべてを終わらせる
That's a problem, we'll ask it later
それから問題があります、後で質問します
ok, here we are again thanking the upper echelons
さて、ここで上層部にもう一度感謝します
to give this wonderful speech
この素晴らしいスピーチをするために
let us welcome him with a round of applause
拍手で彼を歓迎しましょう
good
良い
Thanks
ありがとう
First of all, thanks to Vice President Chen
まず、陳副社長に感謝します。
my last introduction
私の最後の紹介
Thank you for the experience here
ここでの経験をありがとう
feel honored today
今日は光栄に思います
Can be invited by Vice President Chen
陳副総統から招待可能
Then I'm here to tell you about sugar
それから私は砂糖について話したいと思います
to be honest
実を言うと
Because what I asked before were all scientific articles
以前質問したのは科学論文ばかりだったので
scientific stuff
科学的なもの
Today I'm going to talk about popular science
今日はポピュラーサイエンスについて話します
it took a lot of time
とても時間がかかりました
prepare again
もう一度準備します
Otherwise I'm actually giving myself a challenge
そうでなければ、私は実際に自分自身に挑戦を与えていることになります
that is often
それはよくあることです
on the sugar side
砂糖の面では
is often asked
よく聞かれる
It is the sugar next to the word and the sugar next to the word
それは単語の隣の砂糖であり、単語の隣の砂糖です
what's the difference
違いは何ですか
what's going on
どうしたの？
Then the content of my speech today
それでは、今日の私のスピーチの内容ですが、
roughly divided into seven parts
大きく7つのパートに分かれています
I mean, in the dipping medicine you got
つまり、あなたが手に入れた浸漬薬の中で
The last paragraph has seven parts that are
最後の段落には 7 つの部分があります。
I will introduce you to this place
この場所を紹介します
at the beginning
初めに
First, let me introduce to you that there are sugar and heels next to the words.
まず最初に紹介しますが、この言葉の隣にはシュガーとヒールがあるということです。
A general introduction to sugar next to the five characters
5 つの文字の横にある砂糖の概要
that first of all
それはまず第一に
There is a definition of sugar next to the word
単語の横に砂糖の定義があります
Then you can know that
そうすればそれを知ることができます
sugar is composed of carbon, hydrogen and oxygen
砂糖は炭素、水素、酸素で構成されています
its molecule is
その分子は
That is Cm, H2O, N
つまりCm、H2O、Nです。
N can be equal or unequal
N は等しい場合もあれば等しくない場合もあります
Then here you can see that
それから、ここでそれがわかります
In fact, the ratio of the number of hydrogens to oxygens
実際、水素と酸素の数の比は、
exactly like your water
まさにあなたの水と同じように
so we just call it carbohydrates
だから私たちはそれを単に炭水化物と呼びます
like this
このような
It is this carbon and this water
それはこの炭素とこの水です
that's on the english side
それは英語側です
In English, we call it Cup Hydrate
英語ではカップハイドレートといいます
Then this Cup Hydrate
それからこのカップハイドレート
You have to take a closer look
皆さんもじっくり見てください。
Because carbon in English is Cup N
カーボンは英語でCup Nだから
The water is Hydrate
水はハイドレートです
But the combination of these two words
しかし、この二つの言葉を組み合わせると、
Remove an N in the middle
真ん中のNを削除
So everyone, please write the English word Cup Hydrate
だから皆さん、Cup Hydrate という英単語を書いてください
You don't write Cup N Hydrate
カップNハイドレートとは書かない
One more N is wrong
もう 1 つの N は間違っています
This is the possible name of Cod N
これはCod Nの名前の可能性があります
Then there is another alias
それから別の別名があります
This is the one that can also be called Sugar
これはシュガーとも言えるものです
This is the name of the wise life
これが賢明な人生の名前です
sugar classification
砂糖の分類
Basically they all have sugar can see
基本的にはすべて砂糖が入っていることがわかります
one is monosaccharide
一つは単糖類
that's a candy
それはキャンディーです
are some of our common
私たちの共通点の一部です
From Five Tangs or Six Tangs
五唐または六唐から
are some simple sugars
いくつかの単糖類です
A disaccharide is two monosaccharides joined together
二糖類は2つの単糖類が結合したものです
three to nine sugar
砂糖3～9個
we call it fructose
私たちはそれをフルクトースと呼びます
This is a translation of the Chinese translation
これは中国語訳の翻訳です
if polysaccharide
多糖類の場合
more than ten polysaccharides
10以上の多糖類
we call it polysaccharide
私たちはそれを多糖類と呼びます
In addition there is
さらに、
real sugar
本物の砂糖
Let's practice layers of sugar
砂糖の層を練習しましょう
then a line like
それから次のような行
this form of sugar
この形の砂糖
Most require two or more
ほとんどの場合は 2 つ以上必要です
Another one is
もう一つは、
Apart from this appearance
この見た目とは別に
It also has this policy
こんなポリシーもあります
So this is more than a general biomolecule
つまり、これは一般的な生体分子を超えたものです
more complicated
より複雑
We all know that the river is dry and sour
川が乾いていて酸っぱいことは誰もが知っています
one hair straight face
一本の髪のまっすぐな顔
If it is a half-white paper, it is also an ecological face.
半分白い紙ならエコな顔にもなります。
But the sugar is different, the sugar is the same
でも砂糖は違う、砂糖は同じ
it can, the side can be long
できる、サイドは長くてもいい
And sometimes it's not long and not just one
そして時にはそれは長くなく、一度だけではありません
can be long
長くてもいい
This is a bit more complicated
これはもう少し複雑です
The difference with this sugar is here
この砂糖との違いはここです
Generally speaking, if there is sugar in this category, we place
一般的に、このカテゴリーに砂糖が含まれる場合、
All carbon chiral compounds
すべての炭素キラル化合物
If we put on the carbon hand compound
カーボンハンドコンパウンドを装着すると
Let's talk about this sugar
この砂糖について話しましょう
probably can't be wrong
おそらく間違いではないでしょう
So this time carbs are using it to succeed
そこで今回は炭水化物を成功させるために利用します
So include things like steel sugar, starch, cellulose
砂糖、デンプン、セルロースなども含まれます
Or soaked polysaccharide extraction, etc.
または浸漬多糖類抽出など。
These are sugars with this
これは糖質です
The sugar dipped in sugar refers to some sweet sugar
砂糖に浸した砂糖は、甘い砂糖を指します
such as glucose, fructose, maltose
ブドウ糖、果糖、麦芽糖など
Let's just call it dipped sugar
それを浸した砂糖と呼びましょう
that's because making sugar
それは砂糖を作るためです
We will all pour some sugar is 300 lots
みんなで砂糖を注ぎます（300ロット）
does this have something to do with it
これは何か関係がありますか
then you go directly to see
それなら直接見に行ってください
We usually cannot find the word sugar in water
私たちは通常、水の中に砂糖という単語を見つけることができません
really can't find
本当に見つからない
to see later
後で見る
just found out
たった今わかった
The word sugar was invented by Shiguo in the Five Dynasties
砂糖という言葉は五王朝の石果によって発明されました。
So in the early years of the book
したがって、この本の初期の頃には
The annotation in the management is called fish wild
管理上の注釈は Yuye と呼ばれます
so this makes sense
これは理にかなっています
So if you are in the sugar is in the sea water
だから、もしあなたが砂糖の中にいるとしたら、それは海水の中にいるのです
If you see the word sugar
砂糖という言葉を見たら
that's strange
それは奇妙だ
just very
ただとても
It is the invention of the word
それは言葉の発明です
When you talk about sugar, you will think of this sugar
砂糖と言えばこの砂糖を思い浮かべますね
So this candy is in Taiwan
このお菓子は台湾にあるのですね
It is a very important industry in the early days
初期の段階では非常に重要な産業です
So this used to be our Taiwan government
つまり、ここはかつて私たちの台湾政府でした
a big layoff
大規模な解雇
then here you will see
そうすればここでわかります
Here is a photo I found from two steps
これは2つのステップから見つけた写真です
very old
非常に古い
So the face-to-face words at that time
だからあの時の面と向かっての言葉は
from the right side
右側から
that this is the first
これが最初だということ
it's factory
それは工場です
it's about this
それはこれについてです
Use this dry test to help raw materials
このドライテストを使用して原材料をサポートします
So think of this sugar factory
この製糖工場のことを考えてください
This part reminds me of my old hometown
この部分を聞くと昔の故郷を思い出します
I live in Qigu Township, Tainan County
私は台南県七股郷に住んでいます
The part of Naqigu Township near the sea is Sunyan
ナチグ郷の海に近い部分がスンヤンです。
but come in a little more
でももう少し入ってください
Just go home and get to the West Dome side
そのまま家に帰ってウエストドーム側へ。
It's all kind of dry
なんだか全部ドライだね
it was like this at that time
当時はこんな感じでした
so then will
それで、そうなります
From small to large
小さいものから大きいものまで
grew up in this field
この分野で育った
Because the mother is the employee
お母さんが社員だから
So what I miss most at that time
それで、その時私が最も恋しいのは
If you say that everyone has gone to Yanqi Valley and Yanshan
みんなが燕渓谷と燕山に行ったと言ったら
The one that I miss the most is
私が一番恋しいのは
his evening
彼の夜
That sunset is really beautiful
あの夕日は本当に美しいですね
At night, you can really see the sky full of stars.
夜には本当に満天の星空が見えます。
because you can see it's flat
見ての通り平らなので
As far as the eye can see
目に見える限り
It is more difficult in Taipei now
今の台北ではもっと大変です
The other one is New Years
もう一つはお正月です
This Taipei Qigu Township
この台北七股郷
like a lot of private breasts
プライベートな胸がたくさ​​んあるように
That private breast is actually the best private breast
そのプライベートな胸は実は最高のプライベートな胸なのです
It's about 8-12 taels
8～12テールくらいです
you don't buy that
あなたはそれを買わない
Don't buy the one that weighs more than one catty
1斤を超えるものは買わないでください
Anything over a catty is too old.
1斤以上のものは古すぎます。
but now it's different
でも今は違います
Now they are selling big
今、彼らは大きく売れています
when we raised
私たちが育てたとき
This is about 8-12 taels, the most tender and delicious
これが8～12尾くらいで一番柔らかくて美味しいです。
Otherwise, you can still enjoy
それ以外の場合は、引き続きお楽しみいただけます
that black skin milk
あの黒い肌のミルク
This is a special product of the seven-inch incense
こちらは七寸香の特産品です
So I thought Qigu came from Yantian
だから私はQiguが塩田から来たのだと思った
That is to plant these fields
それはこれらの畑に植えることです
Then this former classmate has
すると、この元同級生は、
Parents need to show up at this job
両親はこの仕事に出席する必要があります
So everyone knew
それでみんな知ってた
many little trains
たくさんの小さな電車
Then pull the cane
それから杖を引っ張ります
Then I went to steal sugarcane and eat it
それからサトウキビを盗んで食べました
So many people have this experience
このような経験をした人はとても多いです
Then you see here, that is to say
そうすると、ここがわかります、つまり
Zhuzhi Pond in Taiwan
台湾の竹池池
It describes the Zhetian
それはZhetianについて説明しています
So you can see Zhetian Luanqin B77
Zhetian Luanqin B77 が見えます
I think you'll see it's all turquoise
全体がターコイズ色であることがわかると思います
big and wide
大きくて広い
Several kilometers, tens of thousands of hectares
数キロメートル、数万ヘクタール
Zhetian
浙天
People along the way call it Green Mud Mud
道沿いの人々はそれをグリーンマッドマッドと呼んでいます
This is because everyone, after growing up
だって、みんな大人になってから
There's everything in this dry field
この乾いた野原にはすべてがある
what has the most snakes
ヘビが一番多いのは何ですか
Mouse, all of these are in it
マウス、これがすべて入っています
And this one is because it looks east and west
そしてこれは東と西に見えるからです
If it gets mixed in, it will be like Ming Geng
混ざったらミンゲンみたいになるよ
just be careful
ただ気をつけてください
So every time you harvest
だから収穫するたびに
I also saw that many creatures ran out of the machine in the past
過去に多くの生き物がマシンから飛び出したのも見ました
Then this bundler B7 talks about Brin
それからこのバンドラー B7 がブリンについて話します
Only save this page to think about the stars
星について考えるためにのみこのページを保存してください
That of course took the dry parts
もちろん乾いた部分も取りました
This page is probably for these women
このページはおそらくこんな女性向けです
So these are trendy things
つまり、これらはトレンドのものです
Of course now
もちろん今も
Your guides have been talking about
あなたのガイドが話していたのは、
life and death woman
生と死の女性
So actually let these Zhetian
それで実際にこれらのZhetianをみましょう
These confinement oils may now be converted to storage
これらの封じ込め油は保管場所に転用される可能性があります
This is some recent development
これは最近の開発です
Then of course this candy because we
それからもちろんこのキャンディーも
have been inseparable from the relationship
その関係から切り離せない存在になっている
Because Taiwan has been selling sugar
台湾は砂糖を売っているから
So a lot of sugar is added to a lot of these foods
したがって、これらの食品の多くには大量の砂糖が添加されています
So you can see something like
したがって、次のようなものを見ることができます
candy biscuit pastry or soda
キャンディビスケットペストリーまたはソーダ
these are
これらは
Can't get rid of sugar
糖質が抜けない
about two months ago
約2ヶ月前
It was reported in the newspaper
新聞で報道されました
United States This is the latest study in the United States
米国 これは米国での最新の研究です
It states that there are approximately 180,000 people worldwide
世界中に約18万人いるとされています
because
なぜなら
love this sugary drink
この甘い飲み物が大好きです
and lose their lives
そして命を落とす
That's mainly because
それは主に次の理由です
Get Diabetes Secondary Sex
糖尿病の二次セックスを取得する
then this question is
それではこの質問は
quite serious
かなり深刻な
that this
これは
me about this drink
私はこの飲み物についてです
like the soda part
ソーダ部分のように
you can see
見ることができます
hard to imagine
想像するのが難しい
I will give you an example
例を挙げます
For chemistry this is very good at doing all kinds of different
化学に関しては、これはあらゆる種類の異なることを行うのに非常に優れています
like this orange soda
このオレンジソーダみたいに
Have you all been back?
皆さんもう戻ってきましたか？
Fanta
ファンタ
I saw it on a certain website, that is to say
とあるサイトで見たのですが、
That factory is making Fanta orange soda
あの工場はファンタオレンジソーダを作っています
I haven't seen it come again
また来るの見たことない
Then it can
そうすればできる
Cases of orange soda are sold
オレンジソーダのケース販売
this is wesp
これはウェスプです
If you are interested, you can also see
興味のある方はこちらもご覧ください
You just go to the petal material store
花びら材料店に行くだけです
then you buy some coloring
それから着色料を購入します
buy some fragrance
香水を買う
and then some sugar
それから砂糖を少々
We also pay attention to color, fragrance and sweetness when doing research
色、香り、甘さにもこだわって研究しています
You almost made this chem soda good
あなたはこのケムソーダをもう少しで美味しくできるところだった
I also brought fragrance here for comparison.
比較のために香りも持ってきました。
everybody
みんな
if interested
興味があれば
you can smell it
あなたはそれを嗅ぐことができます
I have bubble tea essence here
ここにタピオカティーエッセンスがあります
Absolutely the same as the black tea you drink
飲む紅茶と全く同じ
You can't run away if you drink it
飲んだら逃げられない
The second is the flavor of the meat
2つ目は肉の旨み
what is the flavor of your meat
あなたの肉の味は何ですか
It's the instant noodles you eat
それはあなたが食べるインスタントラーメンです
Instant noodles are not beef noodles
インスタントラーメンは牛肉麺ではありません
What instant noodles, those meaty ones
なんというインスタントラーメン、あの肉厚なもの
everything is your taste
すべてはあなたの好みです
Then there are strawberries, don't you know?
それからイチゴもありますね？
strawberry is your parent a lot of strawberry flavor
イチゴはあなたの親です イチゴ味がたくさん
There's also strawberry flavor here
こちらにはストロベリー味もあります
depends on what flavor you want
あなたが望むフレーバーに依存します
we chemists can
私たち化学者はできる
then give me some
それから私にいくつかください
what are you happy about
何が嬉しいですか
Glad that many things belong to chemistry
多くのものが化学に属していることをうれしく思います
It's actually not good for your body
実は体に良くないんです
So here is to remind everyone
そこで、皆さんに思い出していただきたいのが、
because these should drink less
なぜなら、彼らは飲酒量を減らす必要があるからです
Because I'm afraid of polluting the site
サイトを汚すのが怖いので
because of this essence
この本質のせいで
Once I open it up
一度開けてみたら
Maybe you'll smell it later
あとで匂い嗅いでみようかな
great taste
おいしい
if you are interested
もし興味があれば
interested in
に興味がある
include end wanted
終わりが必要なものを含める
If you look at it
それを見てみると
welcome to the front
フロントへようこそ
So when it comes to this candy, we will often encounter it.
ですので、このお菓子に関してはよく遭遇します。
Yi'er's businessman Tang, he would rather buy that candy
Yi'erの実業家Tang、彼はむしろそのキャンディーを買いたいです
Then he will want to find some sugar substitutes, so
そうすれば彼は砂糖の代替品を見つけたいと思うでしょう。
The most commonly used sugar substitute is this saccharin
最も一般的に使用される砂糖の代替品はこのサッカリンです
So far, the problem with saccharin is that some people still say it’s OK.
これまでのところ、サッカリンの問題は、まだ大丈夫だと言う人がいることです。
Some people say that it will come by itself, but there is still no one who is sure about this thing
それは自然に起こるだろうと言う人もいますが、これについて確信している人はまだいません
The other one that everyone often encounters is Aspatine
誰もがよく遭遇するもう 1 つはアスパチンです
Aspatine is a bipectide, which is a biecological sugar
アスパチンは生物生態学的糖であるビペプチドです。
It's actually an Aspatidase
実はアスパチダーゼなのです
This is Fanning Ammon
ファニング・アンモンです
So it's a two amino acid glued together
つまり、2つのアミノ酸がくっついたものです
But the point is here, the point is this
しかし、重要なのはここです、重要なのはこれです
There's a methyl here, so it's a fat rib
ここにメチルがあるので、ファットリブです
It is a fatty rib, the methyl, the fatty rib
脂カルビ、メチル、脂カルビです
So after our body decomposes
だから、私たちの体が腐った後、
i want to hear something
何か聞きたいです
false lips
偽の唇
Because this hydrolysis is to get false lips
この加水分解は偽の唇を作るためです
Then this false lip will be very bad for our body
そうなると、この偽りの唇は私たちの体に非常に悪いでしょう
for example eyes
たとえば目
Many people who drink fake alcohol suffer from insomnia
偽のアルコールを飲む人の多くは不眠症に苦しんでいます
So this is not good for long-term use
なので長期使用には向きません
So if you get a chance to go out and buy coffee
コーヒーを買いに出かける機会があれば
If you see a text next to it called
横に次のようなテキストが表示されている場合は、
school girl call
女子高生の電話
still
まだ
forgotten
忘れられた
I forgot
忘れてた
this one
これです
Aspacatin
アスパカチン
you must not add
追加してはいけません
because the coffee is hot when you add it
コーヒーを入れると熱いので
break down faster
より早く壊れる
False lips will come out
偽唇が出てきます
so what
だから何
usually someone is talking
たいてい誰かが話している
What to say about sugar substitutes
砂糖代替品について何を言うべきか
Here
ここ
I am
私は
there is a personal suggestion
個人的な提案があります
Does not represent any of my positions
私の立場を代表するものではありません
My personal because I got it from Wikipedia
ウィキペディアから拾ったので個人的なものです
to find
見つけるには
I now have a description of him
彼についての説明ができました
everyone to fancy
みんなが空想する
You can easily buy field bureaus
フィールドビューローを簡単に購入できます
but very strange
しかし、とても奇妙です
Tianjutang in Taiwan
台湾の天珠堂
has not been very hot
あまり暑くありませんでした
also can not buy
も買えない
But what I know about this thing is
しかし、この件について私が知っていることは、
I've been through a lot of business interests
私はこれまで多くのビジネス上の関心を経験してきました
In the U.S
アメリカ合衆国で
It has never let this Tianjutang
この天珠堂を決して許したことはありません
Why did you enter the U.S. market?
なぜ米国市場に参入したのですか？
Because those who sold the hall have already
ホールを売った人はすでに
the market occupied
市場が占領された
it doesn't want to let it out
それは外に出したくないのです
Taiwan is following the United States
台湾は米国に追随している
this is a big problem
これは大きな問題です
so in japan
だから日本では
in south america
南アメリカで
in the mainland
在大陸
In fact, many of them use Tianjutang
実際、彼らの多くは天珠湯を使用しています。
So if you have elders
それで、もしあなたに年長者がいるなら、
Then there is the problem of diabetes
そこで問題となるのが糖尿病です
then you really crave sugar
そうすると本当に砂糖が欲しくなるんですね
My suggestion is that you can buy a field bureau
私の提案は、フィールドビューローを購入することです
haven't eaten
食べていない
that leaf
あの葉っぱ
you take it off and wash it
あなたはそれを外して洗います
mouth is very sweet
口はとても甘いです
So the one you really want to eat
それで本当に食べたいのは
can watch
見ることができます
I just provide it as a reference for you
あくまで参考として提供させていただきますので、
So the above is the first bulk I think
以上が最初のバルクだと思います
The second part is to introduce to you
第二弾でご紹介するのは、
These single or double halls we often see in our life
私たちの生活の中でよく見るこれらの単一または二重のホール
Or some introductions of widowed or multiple halls
または未亡人または複数のホールの紹介
We often share the same points in this life
私たちはこの人生で同じ点を共有することがよくあります
before that
それ以前は
I still want to give you
まだあなたにあげたい
That's the simplest thing about this
それがこれについての最も単純なことです
Church structure
堂的結構
have different levels
さまざまなレベルがある
some high school, some college
どこかの高校、どこかの大学
even the elderly
高齢者でも
This is a more professional structure
これはより専門的な構造です
generally speaking
一般的に言えば
Take Pratang's History
プラタンの歴史を知る
There are roughly three ways of expressing
表現方法は大きく分けて3つあります
The first one is feature projection
1つ目は特徴投影です
This feature is the professor
この機能は教授です
190 Nobel Prizes in Chemistry
ノーベル化学賞 190 件
He is because of the recognition of the contribution between the halls
ホール間の貢献が認められたためです
It's his habit to turn into this form
この姿になるのが彼の癖だ
The other professor is an English professor named Harris
もう一人の教授はハリスという英語の教授です
Harris Projection
ハリス投影
He is also a major in German
彼はドイツ語も専攻しています
He likes to turn him into such a form
彼は自分をそのような姿に変えるのが好きだ
we do chemistry
私たちは化学をします
We like to turn the conversation into something like this
私たちは会話をこのようなものにするのが好きです
Because of this configuration we know
この構成により、次のことがわかります。
What kind of position is its replacement actually in?
その後継者は実際にどのような立場にあるのでしょうか？
We will understand its planning
私たちはその計画を理解します
Talk about the half-blank paper we just talked about
先ほど話した半分白紙の紙について話します
Or where is the difference in Ha Giang Sour?
あるいはハザンサワーとの違いはどこにあるのでしょうか？
is at this link at this place
このリンクのこの場所にあります
Ha Jiang acid uses zero acid radicals to link each sugar
Ha Jiang 酸は、各糖の結合に酸ラジカルを使用しません。
so it doesn't get any stereochemistry
したがって立体化学は得られません
If it is half white paper it is an ecological piece
半分白い紙ならエコロジーな一枚
It's AMR half-pink minmin
AMRハーフピンクミンミンです
It also doesn't have any stereochemistry
また、立体化学もありません
but sugar is different
でも砂糖は違います
If you connect this candy with another candy
このキャンディと他のキャンディをつなげると
This place can be down or up
この場所は下でも上でも構いません
You link one sugar and you get two Ken's excesses
キャンディーを 1 つリンクすると、ケンの超過分が 2 つ得られます
This is where it gets complicated
ここが複雑になるところです
What about the second one?
2番目のものはどうですか？
There are several OH positions in one sugar
1つの糖に複数のOH位が存在する
These positions can have the opportunity to connect with it
これらのポジションには、それとつながる機会がある可能性があります
Then the sugar with the side chain we just talked about will come like this
すると、先ほどの側鎖を持った糖はこうなります。
Because it's not only half points it can have other
半額ポイントだけではなく他のポイントももらえるので
It can even sugar
砂糖もできるよ
In that case, the complexity of sugar will be more
その場合、砂糖の複雑さはさらに高くなります
So you have to remember that
だからそれを覚えておかなければなりません
Downward we call AVA
下向きを AVA と呼びます
upward we call beda
上向きに私たちはベダと呼びます
This is up and down
これは上下です
This is such a distinction
こういう区別があるんだね
What about the common lancandy?
コモンランキャンディはどうでしょうか？
One is the opposite side of nucleotide
1つはヌクレオチドの反対側です
It's like RNA we call ribose
私たちがリボースと呼ぶRNAのようなものです
Then if the oxygen is missing at No. 2
そうすると、2番で酸素がなくなったら
This we call deoxyribose
これをデオキシリボースと呼びます
the building blocks of DNA
DNAの構成要素
Then there is another Wuhan sugar, the most common one is ribose
それから別の武漢砂糖があります、最も一般的なものはリボースです
Because of this wood, if you take this
この木のせいで、これを取れば
This place of Yuhao is restored
ユーハオのこの場所が復元されました
reduced sugar
砂糖を減らした
This we call xylitol
これをキシリトールといいます
Xylitol
キシリトール
then this is
それならこれは
You often see it in advertisements, right?
よく広告で見かけますよね？
you saw that ad
あなたはその広告を見ました
you are surprised
あなたは驚いています
He took the lead in that ad
彼はその広告で主導権を握った
a naked head
裸の頭
Do you have
ありますか
feel very strange
とても奇妙に感じる
What does this naked head have to do with this?
この裸の頭はこれと何の関係があるのでしょうか？
Later, just by looking at it, I knew that
後は見ただけで分かりました
this naked head
この裸の頭
Bare head
裸の頭
so he
彼は
The ad took the lead
広告が主導権を握った
come with the bare head
裸の頭で来てください
So everyone feels very
だからみんなとても感じてるよ
think this ad
この広告を考えてください
three very
三很有
creativity
創造性
that in addition
それに加えて
common xylose
一般的なキシロース
The most common is
最も一般的なのは
like glucose
ブドウ糖のような
with glucose
ブドウ糖と一緒に
Everyone
みんな
Glucose and Glucose
グルコースとグルコース
now in our body
今私たちの体の中に
are interchangeable
交換可能です
That swapped this
これを交換したのは
So now there is a passing
それで今は通過点があります
after a pro-acidification
酸性化促進後
it's just the simple fact
それはただ単純な事実です
Let everyone understand the relationship between these two sugars
この 2 つの糖の関係をみんなに理解してもらいましょう
Then the location of this place in the future
そして、将来この場所の場所は
It can be opened into a full
フルオープンも可能です
So we say that glucose is a whole sugar
したがって、グルコースは全糖であると言います
just whole sugar
ただの全砂糖
Then this place can balance
そうすればこの場所はバランスが取れる
Can become a form with two swords and a pure
二刀流と純粋な姿になれる
and then overflow
そしてオーバーフローする
So it will become this CO double sword running to the second carbon
それが第二炭素へ走るこのCO双剣となるのです
At this time, it is called turning into copper sugar
このときのことを銅糖化といいます
Then when the back is relaxed, it becomes this
そして背中を緩めるとこうなります
That's fructose
それは果糖です
So it can be replaced in this place
なのでここで交換可能です
So often we might help learn
とても頻繁に私たちは学習を手伝うかもしれません
Speaking of So-Called Whole or Fructose
いわゆる全糖または果糖と言えば
It's the difference here
ここの違いだよ
fructose
フルクトース
Fructose, you can hear fructose clearly, right?
フルクトース、フルクトースがはっきり聞こえますよね？
Then you should pay attention
それなら気をつけたほうがいいよ
Because this sugar is not only its content
この砂糖は内容物だけではないので、
The second thing to look at is its glycemic index
次に注目すべきことは血糖指数です
It means how quickly it gets into your blood after you eat it
食べた後にどれだけ早く血液中に浸透するかを意味します
Resist your sugar concentration
糖分濃度に抵抗する
sugar smaller and faster
砂糖をより小さく、より速く
So eating jaggery is the fastest
だからジャガリーを食べるのが一番早い
Then we eat instant noodles and rice
それからインスタントラーメンとご飯を食べます
Everyone just had dinner, right?
みんなちょうど夕食を食べたばかりですよね？
rice it belongs to this kind of pra sugar that is aggregated
米はこの種のプラ糖が集合したものに属します
It still needs to be hydrolyzed and made again
まだ加水分解して作り直す必要がある
So it will be slower if you want that.
したがって、それを望む場合は遅くなります。
So if you say you eat fructose
それで、あなたがフルクトースを食べると言った場合
we want to separate fructose
フルクトースを分離したい
If it's real fructose spots like this
本物の果糖スポットならこんな感じ
Then I can assure you that you will eat it
そうすれば必ず食べますよ
It's about to float and go into the blood vessel.
浮いて血管に入っていきそうです。
Therefore, those with a high glycemic index should try to lose weight as much as possible
したがって、血糖指数が高い人は、できるだけ体重を減らすように努めるべきです
The other common six-carbon sugar
もう一つの一般的な六炭糖
Except for praline
プラリネ以外は
This is Pratam
プラタムです
The other is glucosamine
もう一つはグルコサミンです
Napra sugar structure
ナプラ糖の構造
Comparing everyone with Pratam
みんなとプラタムを比べてみる
There will be a difference in the position of No. 2
2位の立場に差が出る
It would have been OH light source fine
OH光源だったらよかったのに
Now become an NH2
今度はNH2になります
This is called Putang Antang
ここはプータン・アンタンと呼ばれています
The other is glucose
もう一つはブドウ糖です
It is the place where No. 6 is oxidized
No.6が酸化しているところです
become an acid
酸になる
Another one is mannose
もう一つはマンノースです
Mannose is the position of No. 2
マンノースは2番のポジション
it flips
それはひっくり返ります
originally under
元々は下にあった
Flip now to top
今すぐトップに戻る
galactose
ガラクトース
this is
これは
For example, the comparison is the position of No. 4
例えば比較するのは4番の位置です
This place was originally under
この場所はもともと下にありました
Flip now to yes up
今すぐ「はい」に切り替えてください
Galactose is the place where 6 minutes of NH2
ガラクトースはNH2が6分間存在する場所です。
In addition, this is salt bath sugar
そしてこれは塩バスキャンディーです
We call it LFVCOS
私たちはそれをLFVCOSと呼びます
Another one is Vamos
もう一つはバモスです
Vamos We do not have
バモスはありません
It is inside the plant
工場内にあります
So the sugar candies that I show here
ここで紹介する砂糖菓子は
It's all inside the cells of our body
それはすべて私たちの体の細胞の中にあります
These sugars that appeared
登場したこれらのいくつかの砂糖
So that is to say
つまり、
if you want to pass the season
季節を越えたいなら
not many seasons
季節があまりない
The amount of sugar does not need to be a lot
砂糖の量は多くなくてもよい
Just these few are enough
この数個だけで十分です
Probably more than 90% reliable
おそらく90%以上の信頼性がある
Another candy that I must introduce to you is stinky liquid acid
もう一つ紹介しなければならないのは、臭い液体の酸です。
This is a nine carbon sugar
これは九炭糖です
The earliest discovery of this smelly acid was from bird's nest
この臭い液体酸の最も古い発見は鳥の巣からでした
this is bird's nest
ここは鳥の巣です
Everyone knows the formation of bird's nest, right?
鳥の巣の形成は皆さんご存知ですよね？
The formation of bird's nest is to use the smelly liquid of swallows
ツバメの巣の形成にはツバメの臭い液体が使われる
and then to form
そして形成する
That's because it's the stinky liquid of swallows
ツバメの臭い液体だから
So we specifically translated this stinky liquid acid
そこで、この臭い液体の酸を特別に翻訳しました。
that's how it came
それがこうして来た
It was very expensive to buy this smelly liquid acid in the early days
初期の頃、この臭い液体の酸を買うのは非常に高価でした
too expensive to lose to gold
金に負けるには高すぎる
that is really expensive
それは本当に高価です
That later is now because you can get from that egg
それは今です、なぜならあの卵から
you can go and get this stinky acid
この臭い酸を取りに行ってもいいよ
So the price will drop a lot all of a sudden.
そのため、価格が一気に大幅に下がります。
So now this thing is cheap
それで今、これは安いです
Then everyone can buy
そしたらみんな買えるよ
Then I'll talk about this stinky acid in a moment
それではこの悪臭のある酸については後ほどお話します
It's a social special paradise about bird's nest
それは鳥の巣に関する社会的な特別な楽園です
good
良い
That
それか
The above are monosaccharides
上記は単糖類です
Next, I would like to introduce you to the introduction of disaccharides.
次に、二糖類の紹介でございます。
The most important thing about double sugar is this folding sugar
ダブルシュガーで最も重要なのはこの折り畳みシュガーです
Nazhe candy is composed of glucose and fructose
ナゼキャンディーはブドウ糖と果糖で構成されています
disaccharide
二糖類
Then you speak with justice
それからあなたは正義を持って話します
sugar is easier to sugar
砂糖は砂糖になりやすい
So if you say it’s easy to get sugar
だから糖質が摂りやすいって言うなら
sugar
砂糖
basically eat less
基本的に食べる量を減らす
In addition, maltose
さらに麦芽糖
That maltose is glucose and glucose
その麦芽糖はブドウ糖とブドウ糖です
Alpha is pointing down
アルファは下を向いています
Then E4 link
次にE4リンク
This disaccharide we call
私たちがこの二糖類と呼ぶものは、
maltose
麦芽糖
and lactose
と乳糖
Everyone has milk
みんな牛乳持ってるよ
Or the baby drinks this milk
それとも赤ちゃんがこのミルクを飲むの？
There are galactose and glucose in it
ガラクトースとブドウ糖が入っている
Then it is hit face up
そして表向きに打たれる
E4 sugar stem chain to link
連結するE4糖幹鎖
When we were young or many people may have this lactose hydrolase in the body
私たちが若い頃、あるいは多くの人が体内にこの乳糖加水分解酵素を持っているかもしれません
So you can successfully hydrolyze this disaccharide
したがって、この二糖類を正常に加水分解できます
into galactose and pula sugar
ガラクトースとプーラ糖に
and then use
そして使用します
but with age
しかし年齢とともに
like me
私のような
lactose water
乳糖水
It's been a long time since I drank
久しぶりに飲みました
That pair of lactose hydrolase will disappear
その一対の乳糖加水分解酵素は消滅します
What will happen if there is a lack
不足したらどうなるのか
When this disaccharide goes directly into the water, you will get lactic acid
この二糖類が直接水に入ると乳酸が生成されます。
So you find it convenient and convenient for me to teach a bunch of lactose
乳糖をたくさん教えるのは私にとって便利で便利だと思うのですね
why is my stomach growling
なぜお腹が鳴るのですか
Half an hour will start to ask for sports cars
30分もするとスポーツカーを求め始めます
so what about this
それで、これはどうですか
Then I showed that no one has this kind of heart
そして私は、このような心を持っている人はいないことを示しました
This lactose hydrolase will disappear
この乳糖加水分解酵素は消滅します
Does it have that kind of lactose in foreign countries?
外国ではそんな乳糖があるのでしょうか？
Probably not available in Taiwan
おそらく台湾では手に入らないでしょう
But I will tell you a way
でも、一つの方法を教えてあげます
This is the only way to die
この死んだ場所は生き続けるだろう
What's the meaning
どのような意味です
You just drink it, drink it, drink it
ただ飲んで、飲んで、飲んで
Pull again and drink again
また引いてまた飲む
trade your body for its memory
身体を記憶と交換する
will guide the lactose hydrolysis membrane to come out again
乳糖加水分解膜が再び外に出るように誘導します
then you can drink again
そうすればまた飲めるよ
That's another way
それは別の方法です
Then I will introduce to you
それではご紹介させていただきます
That's when there's a lot of sugar
糖質が多いときは
Then he put the glucose
それから彼はブドウ糖を入れました
to one four one four
1 4 1 4へ
All sugar dry bonds of 1414
それはすべて 1414 のシュガードライボンドです
then make a ring
それから指輪を作ります
This we call ringhujing
これがリングフージンと呼ばれるものです
that kind of
そのようなもの
This kind of tree you can count it this glucose
この種の木は、このブドウ糖を数えることができます
if it is six
6なら
We call it Afa
私たちはそれをアファと呼びます
if there are seven we call beda
7つある場合はベーダと呼びます
If it's eight we call it Ama
8時ならアマと呼びます
So what is the effect of this kind of Huang Hu Jing?
では、このような黄胡経にはどのような効果があるのでしょうか？
He's here to help deliver the drug
彼は薬の配達を手伝うためにここに来ました
what does that mean i mean
それはどういう意味ですか
These O-curved concepts are actually clear water
これらの O カーブの概念は実際には透明な水です
it's all extra tide
それはすべて余分な潮流です
but in this ring
でもこのリングでは
It is combing water
水をとかしているのです
so everyone
だからみんな
this is a model
これはモデルです
This is the model of loess gold
こちらは黄土金のモデルです
you can see it's red
赤くなっているのがわかります
The red one is tide
赤いのは潮です
out of the tide
潮外
middle part
中間部分
is comb water
櫛の水です
so there are some
だからいくつかあります
it seems that the drug
その薬のようです
it is not easy to dissolve in water
水に溶けるのは簡単ではありません
it will use this loess gold
この黄土金を使用します
to be used as storage
ストレージとして使用する
That is to say it can be used
つまり使えます
The effect of combing water
水をとかす効果
then go take this drug
じゃあこの薬を飲みに行ってください
So this is loess gold
これが黄土金です
most commonly used
最も一般的に使用される
But every time I see this molecule
でもこの分子を見るたびに
I just thought of another one
もう一つ思いついたのですが
Field Circle
フィールドサークル
Everyone should be at Mr.Bona
みんなボナさんのところにいるはずだよ
should always know
常に知っておくべき
But this situation is really like
でもこの状況は本当にこんな感じ
But when I saw this, I thought of another one
でもこれを見て別のことを思い出した
When I was doing Ph.D. and research at Berkeley
私がバークレーで博士号取得と研究をしていたとき
At that time, the Berkeley chemistry department had a very important tradition
当時、バークレーの化学科には非常に重要な伝統がありました。
It's all right, come to the Seminar
大丈夫です、セミナーに来てください
They will definitely prepare two boxes of Bona at 12 o'clock
12時には必ずボナを2箱用意してくれる
and then there's coffee
それからコーヒーです
They invite the speaker to chat with the teachers and students in the department
講演者を学科の教師や学生とチャットするよう招待します。
They finally eat very simple
彼らは最終的に非常にシンプルなものを食べます
They're finally just a piece of bona with a cup of coffee
ついにはコーヒー一杯のおまけになってしまった
Then after eating, chat and go in to listen to the Seminar
食事の後は、おしゃべりしたり、セミナーを聞いたりしてください。
So at that time it was said No Bona, No Seminar
当時は「ノーボナ、ノーセミナー」と言われていました。
So as long as you don't prepare Bona
だからボナを用意しない限り
No one will go to your Seminar
あなたのセミナーには誰も行かないでしょう
No coffee, No can't see
コーヒーがありません、見えません
So our tradition of doing chemistry sometimes coffee
ですから、化学を時々コーヒーにするという私たちの伝統です
The word KAMISHI is also very special
「KAMISHI」という言葉も特別なものです
THURSDAY-TRI
木曜トリ
THURSDAY-TRI THURSDAY
木曜日～三木曜日
So we mean to experiment
つまり、実験するということです
to try to know
知ろうとすること
do you just make it
あなたはそれを作りますか？
Another example is that you
もう一つの例は、あなたが
If it is not circular
円形でない場合
but in a linear
しかし直線的に
put it in this shape
この形に置きます
This is what you often see is starch.
よく見かけるこれがでんぷんです
There are two types of starch
でんぷんには2種類ある
This is linear starch
これは線状デンプンです
That is, all of them use Alpha1414
つまり、それらはすべて Alpha1414 を使用します
rattan cable link
籐ケーブルリンク
Another one is
もう一つは、
Starch with side chains
側鎖のあるデンプン
That is to say, at the place of No. 6
つまり6番の場所で
it can be connected again
再び接続できる
and then form another
そして別のを形成します
So we can see that
それでわかります
this number six is ​​that
この6という数字はそれです
There will be some side chain sugars in it
側鎖糖がいくつか含まれます
This side chain sugar is usually very long
この側鎖糖は通常非常に長いです
This is a characteristic of starch
これはでんぷんの特性です
Then everyone probably
そうすると、きっとみんなも
in the last two weeks
過去 2 週間で
Because the public account has the most pages in Taiwan is this Dudian fan
台湾で最も多くのページを持つ公開アカウントはこの Dudian ファンです
Ladies and gentlemen, there are currently 21 kinds of chemical powders merged by the Department of Health and Hygiene
皆さん、現在、保健衛生省によって統合された化学粉末は 21 種類あります。
Manufacturers will make smart
メーカーは賢く作るだろう
he just adds something
彼はただ何かを付け加えただけだ
like maleic acid
マレイン酸のような
or dry maleic acid
または乾燥マレイン酸
add these things
これらのことを追加してください
to increase flexibility
柔軟性を高めるために
Everyone, if you look carefully
みなさん、よく見てみると
The Department of Health and Health can say that what can be added is fumaric acid
保健省は、添加できるのはフマル酸であると言えます。
Why?
なぜ？
Because this is in our metabolism
これは私たちの新陳代謝の中にあるので、
In the silver gate acid cycle
シルバーゲート酸サイクルの中で
Naturally there will be something like this
当然こういうこともあるだろう
So this is what we have in our body
これが私たちの体の中にあるものです
is safe
安全です
You can add this thing to make it more elastic
これを追加して弾力性を高めることができます
But why are manufacturers different
でもなぜメーカーが違うのか
I will choose this again
またこれを選びます
The price is too smart
価格が賢すぎる
The manufacturer is like this
メーカーはこんな感じ
He is looking for cheap
彼は安いものを探しています
So this is the cheapest
なのでこれが一番安いです
this is the cheapest
これが一番安いです
When this hits water
これが水に当たると
He will be hydrolyzed
彼は加水分解されるだろう
become this thing
こうなる
Oh, he is actually the manufacturer.
ああ、彼は実はメーカーなのです。
He just wants to choose cheap
彼は安いものを選びたいだけです
And he doesn't care about other people's lives
そして彼は他人の人生を気にしません
so everyone here
だからここにいるみんな
I always thought it was a class with a chemist student
ずっと化学の学生の授業だと思ってた
I always talk
私はいつも話します
You study chemistry and science
あなたは化学と科学を勉強します
You must have a compassionate heart
慈悲の心を持たなければならない
You must not go to those harming something
何かを傷つけている人たちのところに行ってはいけません
go go go go make money
行って、行って、お金を稼いでください
So folks, because in the lives of students
皆さん、学生の生活の中で
you can get some
いくつか手に入れることができます
something poisonous
何か毒のあるもの
some bad
いくつか悪い
for example
例えば
you will get swimming
あなたは泳げるようになります
Swimming, you see who is unhappy, you have to return him to the cage
泳いでみろ、誰が不幸か分かるだろう、彼を檻に戻さなければならない
I used to meet students at Tsinghua University who said
私はかつて清華大学の学生に会ったことがありますが、こう言いました。
Finishing the water is another matter
水を終わらせるのは別の問題です
Another one is about liking a girlfriend
もう一つはガールフレンドを好きになることについてです
because girls
なぜなら女の子は
want to say make her sick
彼女を病気にして言いたい
Let her go to the hospital to take care of her
彼女を病院に行かせて世話をしてもらいましょう
Just wanted to say in her drink
彼女の飲み物の中で言いたかっただけです
put poison on her
彼女に毒を盛る
She gave her dogs
彼女は犬に与えた
Turns out her girl didn't drink
彼女の女の子はお酒を飲まなかったことが判明
It was a guy in her lab who drank
酒を飲んだのは彼女の研究室の男だった
In the end, that man had to undergo kidney dialysis.
結局、その男性は腎臓透析を受けなければなりませんでした。
Then you say these are
それからあなたはこれらはだと言います
how to say that
それをどう言うか
we're all talking about this
私たちは皆このことについて話しています
make a fuss like this
こうやって大騒ぎする
IQ has nothing to do with this kind of IQ
この種のIQにはIQは関係ありません
So sometimes you're smarter
だから時には賢くなることもある
On the contrary, I will do some stupid things more and more
逆にバカなことをどんどんやってしまう
so this is
それでこれは
people also think
人々も考えます
my personal opinion
私の個人的な意見
I still think the font Qunde
私は今でもQundeというフォントだと思います
still the most important
まだ最も重要な
kids teach it well
子供たちはそれを上手に教えます
get it done
終わらせる
In good health
健康状態良好
Then he will always find
そうすれば彼は必ず見つけるだろう
A place suitable for his development
彼の成長にふさわしい場所
like a rope
ロープのように
will always find a suitable land for his development
自分の発展に適した土地を常に見つけてくれるだろう
That
それか
the one we just talked about
私たちが今話したもの
DC diacid these
DC二酸これら
You can use HPLC
HPLCを使用できます
some to check
いくつかテストする
Then there is also the inspection method of this starch.
それから、このでん粉の検査方法もございます。
Usually, points are used to test
通常、ポイントはテストに使用されます。
So what you guys are doing, let's say
それで、あなたたちは何をしているかというと、
you have high school kids at home
あなたの家には高校生の子供がいます
Or maybe we're doing some high school kids
それとも高校生のことをやっているのかもしれない
you usually learn that
あなたは通常それを学びます
Use dots to test starch
ドットを使用してデンプンをテストする
is there any
何かありますか
That means you just add
つまり、追加するだけです
Point in the water will become
水中の点は次のようになります
Iz-h
イズ・ハ
will then become
そうなると
half heavy color
半分濃い色
but if it has come into existence
しかし、もしそれが存在したとしたら
you will become very deep
あなたはとても深くなるでしょう
blue
青
blue purple color
青紫色
then this
それからこれ
everybody
みんな
this sandalwood
この白檀
If you didn't pay back
返済しなかったら
is open
開いています
it will have
それは持っています
sort of like a spiral
螺旋のようなもの
that this spiral
このスパイラルを
like that shows
それが示すように
that this
これは
You can see that
それがわかります
this dot molecule
このドット分子
I just mentioned
先ほども言いましたが
spiral
螺旋
that
それか
that shot hit
そのショットが命中した
The slow part in the middle belongs to crisp water
真ん中の遅い部分はさわやかな水に属します
So point molecules can run into it
したがって、点分子がそこに衝突する可能性があります
It doesn't exist as I3-4 when you run there
そこを走るとI3-4として存在しません
It is based on I2
I2に基づいています
For point molecules
点分子の場合
what color is the molecule itself
分子自体は何色ですか
It's very masculine
すごく男らしいですね
that color is laid out
その色が配置されています
So you can use that to detect
したがって、それを使用して検出できます
The presence of this starch
このでんぷんの存在が
everyone at the night market
ナイトマーケットのみんな
Or you don't have a shop at home
それとも家にお店がないのか
You always go to buy this pen
あなたはいつもこのペンを買いに行きます
How does the end note pen identify this end note
エンドノートペンはどのようにしてこのエンドノートを識別するのでしょうか
That's actually very simple
それは実際にはとても簡単です
because normal paper
普通紙なので
We're all made of ginger paper
私たちはみんなジンジャーペーパーでできている
When the paper was just finished
ちょうど論文が完成したとき
Actually they are bumpy
実際にはでこぼこしています
And all these companies that make paper
そして紙を作るこれらすべての会社
It's going to treat its surface with ginger
表面を生姜で仕上げます
Then this paper will be very average
そうすれば、この論文は非常に平均的なものになるでしょう
very nice, so you can use
とても素敵なので、使っていただけます
Well, this is also a normal paper dismantling.
まあ、これも普通の紙解体です。
paper, which is made of cotton and thin cloth as cotton
綿と綿のような薄い布でできた紙
So we usually use this book
だから私たちは普段この本を使っています
Or the material you are holding is paper
または、あなたが持っている素材は紙です
are pulped
パルプ化されている
There is no Chaohua, so Chaohua touches the water
ChaohuaがいないのでChaohuaが水に触れます
It's okay, it can be dried and used
大丈夫、乾燥させて使えます
When the paper touches water, don't say that it will be polluted if the saliva is sprayed on it.
紙が水に触れたとき、唾液がかかると汚れるなどとは言わないでください。
That's because of the slurry treatment on it
それはスラリー処理が施されているためです
So what is the general super ratio for?
では、一般的なスーパーレシオとは何でしょうか?
there is nothing in it
そこには何もありません
It's just a little bit easier, it's as simple as that
それはほんの少し簡単です、それは同じくらい簡単です
So that is to say, today if you take your color printer
つまり、今日、カラー プリンタを持っていくと、
Then I went to be this two thousand yuan
それから私はこの2000元になりました
You print it out, then take it and buy it again
プリントアウトして持ち帰ってまた購入する
Of course it can hold that pen
もちろんペンも収納できます
how to get dark blue
ダークブルーを手に入れる方法
it says you take that
それはあなたがそれを取ると言います
That piece of ordinary paper went in
あの普通の紙が入った
So this is how they identify super
これがスーパーを識別する方法です
But I always feel that some people who specialize in printing counterfeit banknotes are still very powerful
しかし、偽紙幣の印刷を専門とする一部の人々は依然として非常に強力な力を持っているといつも感じています。
He always had the ability to get paper that wasn't this ordinary
彼はいつも、これほど普通ではない紙を手に入れる能力を持っていた
always take this special paper
この特別な紙を常に持ってください
The most special thing is that most people can't buy it
最も特別なことは、ほとんどの人がそれを購入できないことです
It is usually the country that goes with a specific
通常、特定の政策に取り組む国です。
printing paper
印画紙
Ladies and gentlemen, let's talk about the report
皆さん、レポートについて話しましょう
i think i seriously misremembered
重大な記憶違いだったと思う
I didn't see the report a while ago
しばらく前にレポートを見ていなかった
North Korea is the best
北朝鮮が一番いいよ
North Korea prints a lot of dollar bills
北朝鮮はドル紙幣を大量に印刷している
Do you have
ありますか
His reports are North Korean diplomats
彼の報告者は北朝鮮の外交官だ
he has a very important responsibility
彼には非常に重要な責任がある
He wanted the hundreds of thousands of fake dollar bills that were given to him in the country
彼は国内で渡された何十万枚もの偽ドル紙幣が欲しかった
be responsible for turning it into real money
それを実際のお金に変える責任があります
then shipped back
その後返送されました
So his production is really beautiful
彼の作品は本当に美しいです
Almost all machines are useless
ほぼすべての機械が役に立たない
This is really the report
本当にこれがレポートです
It's mentioned in the west
西側でも言われてるよ
Another thing related to this is glycogen
これに関連するもう一つのことはグリコーゲンです
glycogen in our body
私たちの体内のグリコーゲン
It is accumulated in the liver
肝臓に蓄積される
Glycogen is the same as the starch just now
グリコーゲンは先ほどのでんぷんと同じです
In fact, starch with side chains is very similar to
実際、側鎖を持つデンプンは、
It's also all Alpha-14 or Alpha-16 links
また、すべて Alpha-14 または Alpha-16 リンクです
But this part of its side chain is relatively short
しかし、側鎖のこの部分は比較的短いです
Can the starch we just talked about be chained for a long time, right?
先ほどのデンプンは長時間連鎖できるんですよね？
Glycogen is shorter
肝糖比較短
That's what glycogen looks like
グリコーゲンってこんな感じです
so after we ate
それで私たちが食べた後
Will eat after carbohydrates
炭水化物の後に食べる
Excess is stored in the liver
余分なものは肝臓に蓄えられる
That excess will sometimes easily form this fatty liver
その過剰が脂肪肝を形成しやすい場合があります
So guys, if you guys go for that ultrasound
それで、皆さん、超音波検査に行くなら
The doctor said, why does your liver look brighter?
医者は、「なぜあなたの肝臓は明るく見えるのですか？」と言いました。
then you have to be a little tight
それなら少しきつめにしなくてはなりません
Because when the five internal organs look dark, right?
だって、内臓が暗く見える時ってありますよね？
If it is brighter, it is a tendency to have a fatty liver
明るいと脂肪肝の傾向あり
Then you would even say that your liver may be the first half of
そうすれば、あなたの肝臓は肝臓の前半部分にあるかもしれないとさえ言うでしょう。
come a little bigger
もう少し大きくなって来てください
So how do we avoid fatty liver or diabetes
では、どうすれば脂肪肝や糖尿病を回避できるのでしょうか？
I actually think we're pretty much experts
実際、私たちは非常に専門家だと思います
Because of avoidance of serious treatment
重篤な治療を避けるため
So the home of preventive medicine
予防医学の本場です
avoidance of attention
避防重視療
so notice what
それで何に気づいてください
sports
運動
snack sugar sports
スナックシュガースポーツ
this is the most important
これが最も重要です
but i went to the doctor
でも医者に行きました
I almost freaked out after I saw the doctor
医者に診てもらった後、びっくりしそうになった
we all get sick sometimes
私たちは皆、時々病気になります
no time to exercise
運動する時間がない
Hello students
こんにちは学生たち
Then the next sentence is to say
すると次の文はこうなります
You don’t take care of your health now, you want to take care of a doctor
あなたは今、自分の健康に気を配るのではなく、医者の世話をしたいのです
so really want to
だから本当にしたい
everyone can spare more time
誰もがもっと時間を費やすことができる
able to exercise more
もっと運動できるようになった
Then talk about this Tuantan
それからこのトゥアンタンについて話してください
what we just said
私たちが今言ったこと
You if you can use your body to move
体を動かすことができれば、
it is capable
それは有能です
it's not powerless
それは無力ではない
so you can move around
移動できるように
Take the hepatopancreas in your liver to eliminate
肝臓にある肝膵臓を取り出して除去します。
But some people are just poor
でもただ貧乏な人もいる
He can't use this way
彼はこの方法を使えない
what is this
これは何ですか
so-called genetic disease
いわゆる遺伝病
Guys, he heard it a while ago
みんな、彼は少し前にそれを聞いた
hepatoenteropathy
肝腸炎
There are so-called back municipalities
いわゆる裏自治体があります。
Speaking of this back-to-back municipal
この背中合わせの自治体といえば
Be sure to listen to the seniors of our former Holy Medical Institute
旧神聖医学研究所の先輩たちの話をぜひ聞いてください
It is our Academician Chen Yiren
私たちのアカデミー会員、陳宜仁です。
He just developed this
彼はこれを開発したばかりです
Millet Long
Millet長
This is a glucose hydrolase
これはグルコース加水分解酵素です
Then he can come and hydrolyze this
そうすれば彼は来てこれを加水分解できる
accumulate this liver
この肝臓を蓄える
can come and save these little kids
来てこの小さな子供たちを救ってください
So because of this success story
この成功事例のおかげで
Hawaii also made it into a movie
ハワイも映画化されましたね
Also recruited two famous stars
2人の有名スターも採用
Harrison Ford splits school with this Brandon
ハリソン・フォード、このブランドンと学校を別れる
right
右
everybody
みんな
when we saw this picture
私たちがこの写真を見たとき
I looked at the back one very carefully.
裏側をじっくり観察してみました。
back
戻る
The structure of the above plate is really good or bad
上のプレートの構造は本当に良いのか悪いのか
This is an M.I possible
これはM.Iの可能性があります
Then he made several
それから彼はいくつか作りました
that's all right
大丈夫です
so he really is
だから彼は本当にそうだ
i need someone special to go
特別な人に行ってもらいたい
to draw over there
そこに絵を描く
Actually I think
実は私はそう思います
That's Penguin
それはペンギンです
That's glucose hydrolase
それはグルコース加水分解酵素です
what is he holding
彼は何を持っていますか
very conceptual
非常に概念的な
that this
これは
I think they are great actors
彼らは素晴らしい俳優だと思う
seems to drive well
運転が上手なようです
just very special
ただとても特別な
the other one is
もう一つは
polysaccharide kidney
腎臓多糖類
You see some
いくつか見えますね
a pure disease
純粋な病気
That is to say, the hydrolytic enzyme that your body lacks
つまり、身体に不足している加水分解酵素です。
which then leads to the accumulation of these sugars
それがこれらの糖の蓄積につながります
So this is some kind of acidic polysaccharide
つまり、これはある種の酸性多糖類です
Then it will cause the accumulation of this cell
そうなると、この細胞の蓄積が引き起こされます
Then this accumulates in the head
そうすると頭の中に溜まっていく
Like this accumulates in the eyes, right?
こうやって目に溜まるんですよね？
eyes will swell
目が腫れます
accumulated in the head
頭の中に溜まった
swollen
腫れた
Then get fat in the heart
そうすれば心も太ります
So these years polysaccharide
それで最近は多糖類
It's really hard for the baby in the court, very poor
法廷にいる赤ちゃんにとっては本当に大変だ、とても可哀想だ
I think you should have
そうすべきだと思います
have you seen these reports
これらのレポートを見ましたか
That's a genetic disease
それは遺伝性の病気です
It's not the kid's fault
その子のせいじゃないよ
This is a parental home review
実家のレビューです
why do you say that
なぜそれを言うのですか
Because all of this is because
なぜなら、これらすべては、
you need a pre-marital health check
結婚前に健康診断を受けなければなりません
This is very important
これはとても重要です
You must first understand what is inside your body
まずは自分の体の中に何があるかを理解する必要があります
Do you have a recessive gene like that?
そんな劣性遺伝子あるんですか？
if your dad has
あなたのお父さんが持っているなら
Your mother will try to find
お母さんが探してみるよ
If your father and mother have
お父さんやお母さんが持っているなら、
you have a one in four chance
あなたには4分の1のチャンスがあります
just as if
まるで
But here in Taiwan
でもここ台湾では
It just so happens that there is such a history
たまたまそういう歴史があったということですね
and he gave birth to a
そして彼は子供を産んだ
He wants to bet a second time
彼はもう一度賭けたいと思っています
He gave birth to three
彼は3人を産んだ
what do you say
あなたは何を言っていますか
sometimes to god like this
時にはこうやって神様に
so this is very important
これはとても重要です
You must have a pre-marital health checkup before you get married.
結婚する前に婚前健康診断を受けなければなりません。
put some of these
これらのいくつかを入れてください
you have to pay special attention to things
あなたは物事に特別な注意を払わなければなりません
In Australia, the B-valve of Minlutan VII is particularly high
オーストラリアでは、ミンルータン VII の B バルブが特に高い
This is for your reference
これはご参考までに
Next, I will introduce to you the little tree
次にご紹介するのは小さな木です
Few trees, walk outside, plants are abundant in every way
木はほとんどなく、外を歩くと、あらゆる面で植物が豊富です
fresh tree, if the leaves are picked off
葉を摘み取れば生の木
Enlarge the leaves, and enlarge this place again
葉っぱを大きくして、またここを大きくして
Zoom in on the chair again and you'll see glucose here
椅子をもう一度ズームインすると、ここにブドウ糖が表示されます。
It's all glucose
全部ブドウ糖だよ
so link up
だからリンクしてください
this one, its
これ、それ
Here's the link, it's all using Bella 1,4
ここにリンクがあります。すべては Bella 1,4 にあります
It is different from the starch dry tank just now
今までのでんぷんドライタンクとは違います
The starch dry tank just now uses α1,4
先ほどのでんぷん乾燥タンクはα1,4を使用しています
Bella
ベラ
Bella 1,4, you will see its structure
Bella 1,4、その構造がわかります
It has intramolecular clarity and intermolecular clarity
分子内透明性と分子間透明性を備えています。
even have a face-to-face meeting
甚至有面跟面的清見
So the one on this side looks relatively flat
したがって、こちら側のものは比較的平らに見えます
different
違う
Could it be the person just now talking about what a computer is?
もしかして、それは今コンピューターとは何かについて話している人物でしょうか?
You will choose right? The first number is not, the first number is flat
選択しますよね? 最初の数字は違います、最初の数字はフラットです
Then why do people eat powder to provide energy? Eating grass does not work
ではなぜ人はエネルギー補給のために粉を食べるのでしょうか? 草を食べても効果はありません
Then this is very simple, because we only have Ah Fa, the bathroom does not need to charge money
それから、これは非常に簡単です、私たちはAh Faしか持っていないので、トイレにお金を請求する必要はありません
We don't have a backup, we don't have a backup bathroom don't charge very much
予備もないし、予備のトイレもないし、料金もあまりかからない
So people are happy for food, not food
つまり人々は食べ物ではなく食べ物に満足するのです
Of course it will help you defecate and lose weight, it won't be cheap
もちろん、排便と体重減少に役立ちます、それは安くはありません
Those grassy ones, why do most of them eat grass and turn them into powder?
あの草っぽい奴ら、なぜ奴らのほとんどは草を食べて粉にするんだ？
The exception is often, let's say ordinary grass, as its stomach is more
例外は、たとえば普通の草です。
It's not like we have only one stomach, it has several stomachs
私たちの胃は一つだけではなく、複数の胃があるのです
Inside one of the stomachs, it has cells
片方の胃の中には細胞があります
Bacteria, Bacteria has this Bebais glucose dumpling in it
バクテリア、バクテリアにはこのベバイスブドウ糖団子が入っています
so it can break down this fiber
この繊維を分解することができます
So look at this food-based animal, after it eats the food
この食用動物を見てください、食べ物を食べた後
It will have a stomach left to grind it first
最初に粉砕する胃が残っているでしょう
After grinding, then it will reflect whether there is
研削後、あるかどうかが反映されます
It's the current that goes to the mouth, and then stirs again
口に流れてまたかき混ぜる
Then it will swallow the stomach inside
そして胃を中に飲み込んでしまう
That's it, that's why we're different
それがそれ、だから私たちは違うのです
As soon as we ate it we went down a bit
食べたらすぐに少し落ち込みました
There is only one stomach, and their ingredients are different
胃は一つしかなく、それぞれの成分が異なります
Another one that you often hear is keting seeds
よく聞くもう 1 つの方法は、種子のケッティングです。
This ketone seed, usually in the false insect
このケトン種子は通常偽昆虫の中にあります
There are fake worms in the empty worms
空のワームには偽のワームが入っています
or this crab
それかこのカニ
or shrimp
またはエビ
There are a lot of these chitin seeds in this shell
この殻の中にはキチン質の種子がたくさん入っています
So everyone is hearing that in the park
だから公園でみんながそれを聞いている
science park
サイエンスパーク
It's really just that there are people who specialize in collecting these shells.
この貝殻を集めている人が本当にいる
That is to say, you are the shrimp moon, and you are the meat inside
つまり、あなたはエビの月であり、あなたはその中の肉です
leave me that shell
その殻は私に残してください
Designing hydrolysis tanks of the hundreds of liters
数百リットルの加水分解タンクの設計
Then do hydrolysis
次に加水分解を行います
I'll talk about it later
それについては後で話します
What will become of it when it is hydrolyzed?
加水分解するとどうなるのでしょうか？
Then you can listen to this fund word
そうすれば、このファンドの言葉を聞くことができます
It is grape goose
グレープグースです
Then it's all about the medical links
それから重要なのは医療関連です
So this place it links to
つまり、この場所にリンクしています
It is very similar to the cellulose you just mentioned
さっき言ったセルロースによく似ています
belong to this form
このフォームに属します
Then I will introduce to you
それではご紹介させていただきます
The third part is about
第三部については、
Introduction of sugary health food and medicine
甘い健康食品や医薬品の紹介
what about the first one
最初のものはどうですか
I'm going to tell you about
についてお話します
Gule Shami
ギュル・シャミ
This is what I just said
これは私が今言ったことです
Are you going to collect a lot of these shells, right?
この貝殻をたくさん集めるつもりですよね？
Then it hydrolyzes it
そうすると加水分解されます
it does hydrolysis what does it use to do hydrolysis
加水分解を行います。加水分解を行うために何を使用しますか
with hydrochloric acid
塩酸で
After the hydrochloric acid is hydrolyzed
塩酸が加水分解された後
These will also be hydrolyzed
これらも加水分解されます
So what you get is
それで、あなたが得るものは
Salts of hydrochloric acid of grape goose
グレープグースの塩酸塩
Then we measure this thing by
次に、これを次のように測定します。
Therefore, lacto acid shows that it is translated directly in English.
したがって、乳酸は英語で直訳すると表示されます。
So lactoamine is translated into Gulesamin
ラクトアミンはグレサミンと訳されます。
I ask you classmates
クラスメートに聞きます
If we can be called Grape Anton
グレープアントンと呼べるなら
heart nothing special
心は特別なことは何もない
the problem is here
問題はここにあります
gluxamine
グルキサミン
it's in the blood
それは血の中にある
It's the same as glucose
ブドウ糖と同じだよ
It will combine with the Nido Tree Society
ニドツリー協会と合併します
So if you say you have elders
それで皆さん、年長者がいると言うなら、
So someone is taking Gulesamin
誰かがグレサミンを服用している
You should pay attention to whether you have diabetes yourself
自分自身が糖尿病であるかどうかに注意する必要があります
because it goes the same way
同じように進むから
we eat glucose
私たちはブドウ糖を食べます
like your blood sugar
血糖値のように
High glycogen levels in the blood
血中のグリコーゲン濃度が高い
Because it's the Nido tree that's going to combine with it
合体するのはニドの木だから
this too
これも
This man is actually exactly the same
この人も実は全く同じだ
So if you take Gulesamin
グレサミンを服用すると
be very careful
十分気をつける
Just be careful with diabetics
糖尿病の人だけ気をつけてね
The problem is below here
問題はここの下にあります
Because of this Gulsamin
このグルサミンのせいで
It is said that the market has hundreds of millions
市場には数億個あると言われています
So everyone has gone to that mass factory
それでみんながあの大量工場に行ってしまった
because it's a bunch of
の束だから
we want it to use
私たちはそれを使って欲しいのです
Is this thing useful?
これは役に立ちますか？
Can it really improve joints?
本当に関節を改善できるのでしょうか？
I don't think anyone has tried this either
これも試した人はいないと思います
Everyone says we've used a lot of experts
多くの専門家を利用したと誰もが言う
In fact, the answer we got
実際、私たちが得た答えは、
The poop tells us it's a placebo
うんちはそれがプラセボであることを教えてくれます
It is what Master often said, peace of mind will bring peace
マスターがよく言っていた言葉です、心の平和が平和をもたらします
Do you think it's useful if you eat it
食べたら役に立つと思いますか？
it will be fine
大丈夫だよ
this is sometimes in my heart
これは時々私の心の中にあります
This idea is also important
この考え方も大切です
but true is not valid
しかし、trueは無効です
Everyone, it's theoretically like this
皆さん、理論的にはこうです
It is wished to say that you ate this Gule Shami
このグレシャミを食べたと言いたい
Then your body will synthesize
そうすればあなたの体は合成します
right
右
then you deep synthesis
それからあなたは深層合成をします
deep synthesis of something
何かの深層合成
hyaluronic acid
ヒアルロン酸
right
右
Hyaluronic acid is hot right now
今ヒアルロン酸が熱い
you want to wrinkle
しわを寄せたいですか
or to
またはへ
inside our eyes
私たちの目の中に
That's our Bo Li translation called hyaluronic acid
それはBo Liの翻訳で、ヒアルロン酸と呼ばれています
Is the surface of our eyes smooth?
私たちの目の表面は滑らかですか？
Right?
右？
That's hyaluronic acid in it
ヒアルロン酸が入っているんですね
Our knees should be lubricated
私たちの膝には潤滑油が必要です
So this hyaluronic acid is produced
そこでこのヒアルロン酸が生成されるのです
hyaluronic acid content
ヒアルロン酸含有量
it is a polymer
それはポリマーです
The higher the quality, the better
品質が高ければ高いほど良い
because of its water absorption
吸水性があるので
the highest moisture content
最も高い水分含有量
You'll have to look it up on Wikipedia
ウィキペディアで調べる必要があります
what hyaluronic acid
ヒアルロン酸って何？
highest quality
分質量最高
Machine irrigation
機械灌漑
The hyaluronic acid in it has the highest quality
配合されているヒアルロン酸は最高品質
Than you use the way I live
あなたが私の生き方を利用するよりも
Than what planning method do you use
どのような計画方法を使用するかよりも
Chemical methods are even better
化学的方法はさらに優れています
But I need to say something like this today
でも今日はこういうことを言わなきゃいけないんです
don't want
不要
So we are going to be killed
それで私たちは殺されることになる
no inside most true
内側は最も真実ではありません
then hopefully
それからできれば
We are all like this hyaluronic acid
私たちは皆、このヒアルロン酸のようなものです
but you can see
しかし、あなたは見ることができます
these hyaluronic acid
このヒアルロン酸
It is the composition of putao acid sugar
プタオ酸糖の組成です
One is putao acid sugar
一つはプタオ酸糖です
The other one is N to CG putao acid sugar
もう一つはN to CGプタオ酸糖です
so if you really want to eat
だから本当に食べたいなら
which one we will suggest you to eat
どれを食べるかお勧めします
eat this
これを食べて
N to CG's Putao acid sugar
N to CGのプータオ酸糖
because after eating it
食べた後だから
will not immediately enter the degree
すぐに学位を取得することはできません
Same as Putao
プータオと同じ
To combine with Ijima tree
居島木と組み合わせるには
this is what you need to prove
これはあなたが証明する必要があるものです
so this
したがって、この
Won't make you a problem with diabetes mellitus
糖尿病の問題を引き起こすことはありません
if say you want to eat this
これが食べたいと言ったら
if you think it's not enough
十分ではないと思うなら
you don't add this
あなたはこれを追加しません
because it forms sugar
糖分が生成されるので
Yes need two sugar
はい、砂糖が2つ必要です
so many
とてもたくさんの
now you go to that
今、あなたはそこに行きます
The kind of biotech company that sells drugs
医薬品を販売するバイオテクノロジー企業の一種
start many recipes
たくさんのレシピを始める
Just the price of sugar
砂糖の値段だけ
Various recipes from companies other than their own
自社以外のレシピも多数
This is what it says
こう書いてあります
It's that simple
それはとても簡単です
So the main meaning is
したがって、主な意味は次のとおりです
ornithium
オルニジウム
The other one is that you usually put it in the advertisement
もう 1 つは、通常、広告に掲載することです。
see the so-called gnosis polysaccharide
いわゆるグノーシス多糖体を参照
Especially the former Chinese anchor
特に元中国人アンカー
Ms. Xuan Miyang
スアン・ミヤンさん
Advertisement of Grape Network, right?
グレープネットワークの広告ですよね？
The polysaccharides that are also gnostic also eat a lot
グノーシス系である多糖類もよく食べる
Everyone, polysaccharides of Gnosis
皆さん、グノー​​シスの多糖類
How to kill cancer cells
がん細胞を殺す方法
Polysaccharides do not kill cancer cells
多糖類はがん細胞を殺さない
Polysaccharides are what you need to be able to get into your gut
多糖類は腸内に入るために必要なものです
enter the stomach here
ここから胃に入ります
Then the water and blood components are made into smaller things like this
すると、水と血液の成分がこんなふうに小さくなります。
and then to the intestines to stimulate your immune system
その後腸に送られて免疫システムを刺激します
Then your immune system goes to fight the cancer cells
その後、免疫システムががん細胞と戦い始めます
So this thing itself will not kill cancer cells
つまり、これ自体はがん細胞を殺すわけではありません
So please don't get it wrong
だから誤解しないでください
that this one
これは
polysaccharides
このタイプの多糖類
mostly this kind of glucose
ほとんどがこの種のブドウ糖
Then practice it with Beda 1 3 1 3 sugar tip
次に、Beda 1 3 1 3 シュガー チップで練習します。
with practice it will work
練習すればうまくいきます
this is the most
これが一番
This is the basic stock price
これが基本株価です
Usually there are some single tangs connected at the 6th place
通常、6 番目の位置にいくつかの単一のタングが接続されています。
It may be Grape Church, it may be Yuanzao Church, it may be others
それはブドウ教会かもしれないし、元蔵教会かもしれないし、その他かもしれない
A variety of these possible single tangs
これらのさまざまな単一のタングが考えられます
But so far, there is still no solution for this
しかし今のところ、これに対する解決策はまだ見つかっていない
Why? Because what is the composition of these things in practice
なぜでしょうか? 実際にはこれらの要素はどのような構成になっているのでしょうか?
It's still unclear
まだ不明です
This includes our dean, who is also working on this part
これには、この部分にも取り組んでいる学部長も含まれます
There is another one that I want to mention to you is the so-called Gansu
もう一つお話ししたいのは、いわゆる甘粛省です。
Gansu
甘粛省
I'm doing it, if you have elders, if I'm doing some kind of chemotherapy
もしあなたに年長者がいるなら、私が何らかの化学療法を行っているなら、私はそれをやっている
POTA is often used sometimes
POTAは時々よく使われます
POTA sometimes goes to wash for a while
POTAは時々ちょっと洗濯しに行きます
why? because it clots the blood
なぜですか？それは血液を凝固させるからです
That's what you need to use for anticoagulation.
それは抗凝固療法に使用する必要があるものです。
Gansu
甘粛省
a lot of
たくさんの
former Gansu
旧甘粛省
where are they from
彼らはどこ出身ですか
mostly from the mainland
ほとんどが本土から
mainland
大陸
So before the mainland
だから本土の前に
Before 2008
2008年前
Who is the richest person in mainland China
中国本土で一番裕福な人は誰ですか
It's for Gansu
甘粛のためです
Why
なぜ
Because the mainland has a population of 1.3 billion
本土の人口は13億人だから
Do you know how many pigs he kills a day?
彼が一日に何頭の豚を殺すか知っていますか？
you know i'm here you wanna laugh
私が笑いにあなたのところに来たのを知っていますか
He wants to kill tens of millions of pigs
彼は何千万頭もの豚を殺そうとしている
These he put these fields
彼はこれらのフィールドを配置しました
after receiving
受け取ってから
Then go get this Gansu
それなら甘粛省を取りに行ってください
Year 2008
2008年
what's a problem
何が問題ですか
He went to get this Gansu
彼は甘粛省を取りに行きました
He adds other things to you in it
彼はあなたに他のものを加えます
that is
あれは
there was a so-called
いわゆる
over-safety
過剰安全
contrading-safety
安全性の対立
that thing
その事
add that thing
そのことを追加します
he's okay sometimes
彼は時々大丈夫です
want to increase his weight
彼の体重を増やしたい
go bag that one
あれをバッグに入れてください
Turns out that thing is responsible
あれに責任があることが判明
As a result, several people died
その結果、数名が死亡した
So the United States is scared
だからアメリカも怖いんだよ
He specially went to their site to see
彼は特別に彼らのサイトに行って見ました
You can see the power outage like this
停電の様子はこんな感じでわかります
You are under GMP control
あなたはGMP管理下にあります
So the United States is scared
だからアメリカも怖いんだよ
So it becomes to say that from 2008 onwards
ということは2008年以降はこうなる
You want to buy Gansu again
甘粛省をもう一度購入したい
otherwise you can't buy
そうしないと買えない
or low molecular weight Gansu
または低分子量甘水
can't buy now
今は買えません
Why? Because I dare not enter
なぜ? あえて入らないから
so here
それでここで
Everyone see it
みんな見てね
Recently there are some
最近はいくつかありますが、
a dance hall
ダンスホール
this dance hall
このダンスホール
It is specifically used for anticoagulation
特に抗凝固に使用されます
This dance hall body is already a medicine
このダンスホールの体はもう薬だ
already in the US
すでに米国にいる
or here in Europe
あるいはここヨーロッパでも
already a drug
すでに麻薬
We were doing this first
私たちは最初にこれをやっていました
This one is selling pretty well right now.
これ、今かなり売れてます。
its price is quite high
その価格はかなり高いです
So now is to try to make it as low as possible
だから今はそれをできるだけ低くするように努めることです
able to evolve
進化できる
In this case, I hope that in the future, it will be much better if we build our capital and get rich.
この場合、将来的には資本を構築して裕福になったほうがずっと良くなると思います。
This is a stage, a structure
これは舞台であり、構造物です
It can be combined with MHCB so this single
MHCBと併用できるのでこれ一本
It can be used for anticoagulant effect
抗凝固作用がある可能性があります
There are also some anticancer drugs that you often hear
よく聞く抗がん剤もあります。
The most leading one is Xiao Hongmei
最も有力なのはシャオ・ホンメイです
everyone has heard
聞いてますか
Little Red Beauty is all cancer drugs
リトル・レッド・ビューティーはすべて抗がん剤です
Everyone in these classes can see that
これらのクラスの全員がそれを見ることができます
In fact, except for this ring
実はこの指輪を除いては
Three structures on this side of this ring
このリングの手前にある 3 つの構造物
It is very important that it contains a sugar
糖質が含まれていることは非常に重要です
This candy also plays a very important role in helping you
このキャンディーはあなたを助けるためにも非常に重要な役割を果たします
We thus self-satisfy
このようにして私たちは自己感受性を高めます
This mainly means that this place is a flat structure
これは主に、この場所が平らな構造であることを意味します
It will hack into BMA's Migel Roof
BMA の Migel Roof をハッキングします
Larger ore finer places
より大きな鉱石より細かい場所
it will cut into that place
その場所に切り込みます
can then reach
そうすれば到達できる
This anti-cancer effect
この抗がん作用は
that thing
その事
Belly is not small
お腹は小さくない
so it's beautiful when you hit it
だから叩くと美しいんだよ
hair loss
脱毛
Vomit
嘔吐
These questions are often
こういった質問はよくありますが、
Everyone
みんな
recently
最近
many of these drugs
これらの薬の多くは
when you use that viz
そのウィズを使用するとき
Just Liposome
まさにリポソーム
to wrap this
これを包む
the stomach will be much lower
お腹はかなり下がってきます
will reduce a lot
かなり減るだろう
Then
それから
Vomiting will also be reduced a lot
嘔吐もかなり減ります
so everyone
だからみんな
Unfortunately, this old man doesn't have many copies.
残念ながら、この老人はあまりコピーを持っていません。
but you can discuss it with your doctor
しかし、医師に相談することはできます
If the family can afford it
家族に余裕があれば
you can
あなたはできる
Can use
使える
hit this thing
これを叩く
will compare
比較します
It's beautiful when you hit it directly
直撃すると綺麗ですね
came much better
はるかに良くなりました
In addition, some anticancer drugs
また、一部の抗がん剤には
like this is
これのように
This Purel2
このピュアル2
injection
注入
then these are
それからこれらは
i have a lot of people bring it up
たくさんの人にそれを取り上げてもらいました
that is
あれは
these cancer drugs
これらの抗がん剤
it's actually quite sugary
実際にはかなり甘いです
help you get these candies
これらのキャンディーを手に入れるのを手伝ってください
to the doctor
医師へ
it won't work
それはうまくいきません
So many people want to know what role this sugar stone plays
非常に多くの人がこの砂糖石がどのような役割を果たしているのか知りたいと思っています
Does it just increase solubility?
溶解度が上がるだけですか？
It's not that simple
そんなに単純じゃないよ
So this is commonly used, this Cornia
で、これがよく使われる、このコルニア
There are also some antibacterial antibiotics
抗菌作用のある抗生物質もあります
This is made with a lot of bacteria sugar men
これはシュガーマンをたくさん使って作られています
This is specifically for the muddy urine system
これは特に濁った尿システムに適しています。
To deal with that E. coli infection
その大腸菌感染症に対処するには
And like mud urine male mud
そして泥尿のような男性の泥
These are very amine-based
これらは非常にアミンベースです
antibacterial
抗菌
This is also used in our daily life
これは私たちの日常生活でもよく使われています
Ladies and gentlemen, where do you go for the medicine to see your ingredients?
皆さん、薬の成分を見るにはどこに行きますか？
still don't understand
まだわかりません
I don't understand, I need to check
分かりません、確認する必要があります
The current Internet is too differentiated
現在のインターネットは差別化されすぎています
we both have to check
私たち二人ともチェックしなければなりません
So you need to find out what ingredients are in the medicine you used
したがって、使用した薬にどのような成分が含まれているかを調べる必要があります
to know its side effects
その副作用を知るために
This is all available
これはすべて利用可能です
Another is the red cotton tree
もう一つは赤い綿の木です
The red cotton tree is also
赤い綿の木も
So use a lot when you have inflammation
炎症があるときはたくさん使用してください
The same goes for everyone
誰でも同じです
It also has these sugars here
ここにも糖質が入っています
Then these sugars will go to the bacteria
その後、これらの糖は細菌に行きます
The drug is called RNA
その薬はRNAと呼ばれます
and then to be aware of its growth
そしてその成長に気づくこと
That's one of its effects
それもその効果の一つです
Then there is another one
それからもう一つあります
What you often hear is
よく聞くのは、
third line antibiotics
第三線的抗生素
vancomycin
バンコマイシン
Usually when you don't even have this antibiotic
通常、この抗生物質さえないとき
you probably want
あなたはおそらく欲しいでしょう
just be right please
ちょうどいいです、お願いします
because possible
可能だから
some derivatives of it
それから派生したもの
some other variants of it
それの他のバリエーション
If there is no more effective doctor
もっと有能な医師がいない場合
it can't help
それは役に立ちません
So this is already the third line
これはすでに 3 行目です
followed by antibiotics
続いて抗生物質
this is the same
これも同じです
this antibiotic
この抗生物質
It also has the structure of these sugars
これらの糖の構造も持っています
And without this sugar
そしてこの砂糖なしで
its efficacy will be listed
その効能が列挙されます
And our common Chinese herbal medicine
そして私たちの一般的な漢方薬
You have heard of real herbs
本物のハーブについて聞いたことがあるでしょう
that herb
そのハーブ
Many of them are fried or watered.
それらの多くは揚げたり、水を加えたりします。
It doesn't have to be in the water to fry with water
水で揚げるのに水に入れる必要はない
Why don't you drink it? There are a lot of things in it.
飲んでみませんか? いろいろ入っています。
all contain sugar
どれも砂糖が入っている
Let me give you an example
例を挙げてみましょう
The innermost example is hay
最も内側の例は干し草です
hay
干し草
hay this
やあ、これ
This is the main ingredient in it
これが主成分です
this is a special
これは特別です
That is, we start from a sticker class
ステッカークラスから始めるということです
There are also some sugary things over here
ここにも甘いものがあります
that at that time
あの時のこと
hay means
干し草の意味
Some cores for some antiviral aspects
いくつかの抗ウイルス機能を備えたコア
and some like cardiotonic
強心薬のようなものもあります
For us there is a so-called Bitutoxin
私たちにとって、いわゆるビツトキシンがあります。
This category belongs to Cde-Glycoside
このカテゴリは Cde-グリコシドに属します
That is to say, it has a sterol
つまりステロールが入っている
sterols and then sugars
ステロール、そして糖類
This is blown from the flower of a plant in Africa
これはアフリカの植物の花から採取したものです
Then tell me you have a heart problem
それなら心臓に問題があると言ってください
if say you let breath
息を止めたと言うなら
no way heart
まさかの心
the so-called master gill
いわゆるマスターギル
Putting this disability is something that can be proxied
この障害を代理できるものです
Vasodilation
血管拡張
The above is about the general we common these
上記は、これらに共通する一般的な内容です。
Introduction of healthy food or medicine
健康食品や薬の紹介
Then I'm going to talk to him a little bit
それから彼と少し話してみるよ
glucose metabolism
グルコース代謝
I won't go into the details of those
それらの詳細には触れません
step by step metabolism
段階的に新陳代謝
Just to tell you in general
ただ一般的に言っておきますと
let's make an introduction
紹介をしましょう
We ate the usual glucose
いつものブドウ糖を摂取しました
the most important thing is to do
最も重要なことは行うことです
is to be able to generate energy
エネルギーを生み出すことができるということ
what is this energy
このエネルギーは何ですか
is our energy currency
私たちのエネルギー通貨です
That is ATP
それがATPです
what is this
これは何ですか
You can see that
それがわかります
glucose
グルコース
Then essential oil glycolysis
次にエッセンシャルオイルの解糖系
Then get this row
次に、この行を取得します
then this is
それならこれは
No. 2 has a bottle of this acid on the same plane
No.2 は同じ飛行機にこの酸のボトルを持っています
Then what
じゃあ何
Its ATP can be converted into ATP
そのATPはATPに変換できます
And here is its structure
そしてこれがその構造です
Mainly
主に
Here are two bottles of acid
ここに酸のボトルが 2 つあります
This side becomes three bottles of acid
こちら側が酸のボトル3本になります
Then this ATP
するとこのATPは
is what we call energy currency
私たちがエネルギー通貨と呼ぶものです
It can be used to provide energy
エネルギー供給に利用できる
that here
それがここにある
Our glycolysis is also fast
私たちの解糖系も速いです
In this ranking, there are basically hillside map letters that can be walked
このランキングでは基本的に歩いて行ける山腹マップ文字が入っています
We normally take this picture letter of swimming
普段はこの水泳の絵手紙を撮っています
so it will go through the acid cycle
アミノ酸サイクルを通過します
Then finally mix carbon dioxide with water
そして最後に二酸化炭素と水を混ぜます
can then be discharged
その後退院できる
If today, if you are relatively hypoxic
今日、比較的低酸素状態の場合
Then there is a chance that this will turn into halogen acid
そうするとハロゲン酸になる可能性があります
vitamin brine
ビタミンブライン
vitamin brine this side
ビタミンブラインこちら側
it is without oxygen
酸素が無い状態です
it can turn it into an inch
それをインチに変えることができます
so here
それでここで
Often we will be assigned a
多くの場合、私たちは
Why stay up late to practice books or play rehearsal
練習本やリハーサルのために夜更かしする理由
you will feel hungry
あなたは空腹を感じるでしょう
Do you have
ありますか
Will it feel like this at the end
最後はこんな感じになるのかな
It will be better
いずれ良くなるだろう
This is actually
これは実際には
Because our brains use a lot of energy
私たちの脳は多くのエネルギーを消費するので、
energy needed by the brain
脳に必要なエネルギー
is to use sugar to hydrolyze acid
砂糖を使って酸を加水分解することです
it is used very quickly
とても早く使われます
our organs
私たちの臓器
Do our organs also need
私たちの臓器も必要ですか
But the energy our organs need
しかし、私たちの臓器が必要とするエネルギーは
Demolition is not required
解体は必要ありません
Is there only one other mechanism for a carbonless bomb
カーボンレス爆弾の仕組みは他に一つしかないのか
Then if it's the bombardment
じゃあ砲撃なら
This is for your quick access to that energy
これはそのエネルギーに素早くアクセスするためのものです
So you find this place in your brain
それであなたはあなたの脳の中にこの場所を見つけます
do it fast
早くやって
Because you have to think when you are full
お腹がいっぱいになってから考えなければいけないから
other things to think about
他に考えるべきこと
So this consumes quickly
なので消費が早いです
That's why you get this hunger feeling
だから空腹感を感じるんだよ
So it talks about how to break through this one
それで、これを突破する方法について話します
soon
すぐ
Then why do we exercise
ではなぜ運動をするのか
after muscle exercise
筋トレ後
We sometimes get that muscle sore the next day
翌日筋肉痛になることもあります
Is there such a problem
そんな問題あるのか
Then
それから
the next day it was
次の日はそうでした
The amount of oxygen in your thin stomach because of your muscular movement
筋肉の動きによる薄いお腹の酸素量
just not enough
ただ十分ではない
Insufficient
比較不足
then it produces lactic acid
すると乳酸が生成されます
So your muscle soreness is due to lactic acid
あなたの筋肉痛は乳酸が原因です
So lactic acid is not a good thing
だから乳酸は良くないんだよ
in the intestine will excrete your sugar
腸内で糖分が排出されます
That bowel will lactic acid quickly
その腸はすぐに乳酸になります
right
右
so you'll see what you've got
それで、あなたが何を持っているかがわかります
Going this way is more hypoxic and sugary, right?
この道を歩くと、より低酸素で糖分が多くなりますよね？
Did you ever drink alcohol when you were young?
若い頃お酒を飲んだことがありますか?
people may have also tried
人も試したことがあるかもしれない
Because when I was young, I often couldn't help measuring alcohol
若い頃はよくアルコールを計らずにはいられなかったので
open it
それを開く
see what happens
何が起こるか見てみましょう
you will run in with oxygen
あなたは酸素を持って走ります
Then if you run in and drink, you will become something like that
じゃあ駆け込んで飲んだらあんなことになるよ
that vinegar
その酢
So the resulting wine is very sour
出来上がったワインはとても酸っぱいです
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
It's because he walks this way
それは彼がこちらを歩くからです
Your current lip it will go further
今の君の唇はもっと先へ
it may be spring or alcohol
それは春かもしれないし、お酒かもしれない。
Then further oxidation becomes acidic
さらに酸化すると酸になります
So when you measure wine, you measure it into vinegar
つまり、ワインを計るときは、酢を計ることになります。
that this is about this
これはこれのことだということ
I'm going to introduce this side
この辺を紹介していきます
Then I will introduce to you a little
それでは少しご紹介させていただきます
The fifth part is about this sugar on the cell surface
第5回は細胞表面の糖についてです。
Some other biological tools
その他の生物学的ツール
This side is more biased
こっちのほうが偏ってるよ
A little introduction to glycobiology
糖鎖生物学へのちょっとした入門
what about here
ここはどうですか
That's what we use the electron microscope lens
それが電子顕微鏡のレンズです
Then look at this section of the cell
次に、セルのこのセクションを見てください。
So here's the nucleus
ここが核です
then lipid
それから脂質
that this place
この場所が
This place is called the membrane of the cell
この場所は細胞膜と呼ばれます
You see a very deep black thing
とても深い黒いものが見えますね
This is like a layer of sugar
これは砂糖の層のようなものです
so-called sugar republics
いわゆる砂糖共和国
it's on the outside of the cell
それは細胞の外側にあります
So what is the situation with this sugar republic molecule?
では、この砂糖共和国の分子はどうなっているのでしょうか?
It is a very simple deep synthetic soil
とてもシンプルな深層合成土です
For your reference
ご参考に
this is our cell membrane
これは私たちの細胞膜です
There are many pores in our cell membrane
私たちの細胞膜にはたくさんの穴があります
water channel
水路
tunnel of mudstone
泥岩のトンネル
what else is there
他には何があるの
Pores of the bladder
膀胱の毛穴
This kind of tunnel
こんな感じのトンネル
Then the sugar can enter the cell
そうすると糖分が細胞内に入る可能性があります
in this cell
この細胞の中で
In addition to glycolysis
解糖系に加えて
Just like what I just said
今言ったことと同じように
will generate RTP
RTPを生成します
generate energy these
これらのエネルギーを生成します
In addition it can also be transformed into different these nuclear dry water
さらに、これらの異なる核乾燥水に変換することもできます
Snap rod, sorry, snap rod
スナップロッド、ごめんなさい、スナップロッド
What are these for?
これらは何のためにあるのでしょうか？
These are used to make the so-called sugar assembly
これらは、いわゆる砂糖集合体を作るために使用されます
Then it can be used in high-quality subjects
そうすれば、質の高い被写体に使用できます
or internal fat pills
または内部脂肪の丸薬
this part of
この部分の
Synthesize these Sugar Pound Whites right here
これらのシュガーパウンドホワイトの詳細な合成はここにあります
or candy paper
またはキャンディー紙
that sugar pound white
あの砂糖ポンドの白
It depends on whether it is folded perfectly
完璧に折りたためるかどうかによります
It doesn't work if it doesn't fold well
上手く折り畳まないとダメだよ
Those perfectly folded
完璧に折りたたまれたもの
With these candy papers it will
このキャンディペーパーを使えば、
Run from this place to the surface of this cell
この場所からこの細胞の表面まで走ります
So you see that layer
その層がわかります
black is these things
黒はこれらのものです
Sugar Woven Paper and Sugar Pound White
シュガーウーブンペーパーとシュガーパウンド ホワイト
Those things will age too
そういったものも老化していきます
or poorly folded
または折り方が不十分
Where does all this stuff go?
こういったものはどこへ行くのでしょうか？
enter this media
このメディアに入る
It's like a hydrolysis factory in the media
メディアの加水分解工場のようなものです
it will rehydrolyze all these things
これらすべてを再加水分解します
After hydrolysis, you will return to
加水分解後は元に戻ります。
Back to Crown Sugar or Ankisu
クラウンシュガーまたはアンキスに戻る
Then repeat the cycle again
その後、もう一度サイクルを繰り返します
So our cell factory is very
ですから、私たちの細胞工場は非常に
So effectively it's doing this in a loop
事実上、これをループで実行していることになります
it applies to every bit
それはあらゆるビットに当てはまります
it won't go to waste
それは無駄にはなりません
So just look at the whole inside
それで、内部全体を見てください
Like the people's body, do we have the annual certificate we just mentioned?
国民の身体と同様に、私たちも先ほど述べた年次証明書を持っていますか?
The annual certificate is in the people's body
年次証明書は人々の体内にあります
Lack of this submerged coal
この水中石炭が不足している
that's a matter of genetics
それは遺伝の問題です
Then these sugar and molecules will be spread on the surface
そして、これらの糖と分子が表面に広がります
Then it will work with many foreign things
そうすれば、多くの外国のものでも動作します
including viral infections
ウイルス感染症も含めて
city ​​army infection
市軍感染
or with some poison
あるいは何らかの毒を使って
Poisonous mushrooms we often talk about
よく話題になる毒キノコ
Ladies and gentlemen, do you get poisoned when you eat a lot of mushrooms?
皆さん、キノコをたくさん食べると中毒になりますか？
or snake venom
またはヘビの毒
Bitten by a snake is not a venomous snake
ヘビに噛まれても毒ヘビではない
These things will follow the superficial effects
こういったものは表面的な効果をもたらします
So if you want to tell everyone in detail here
なので皆さんに詳しくお伝えしたい方はこちら
probably another two hours
おそらくあと2時間
the virus here
ここのウイルス
Let me give you a very simple introduction
とても簡単にご紹介させていただきます
Because this is related to our personal comparison
これは私たちの個人的な比較に関連するため、
Infectious diseases caused by viruses that are common in Taiwan
台湾で流行しているウイルスによる感染症
Including influenza virus, enterovirus, style stomach, cannon disease, infection virus
インフルエンザウイルス、エンテロウイルス、胃腸炎、大砲病、感染症ウイルスを含む
or pox etc.
または痘瘡など。
Isn't it human? Yang will also
人間じゃないですか? ヤンもそうします
what about this
これはどうですか
about flu virus
インフルエンザウイルスについて
You can see that there is emotion
感情があることがわかります
or pigs feel
あるいは豚は感じる
or people
または人々
human flu
人間のインフルエンザ
Everyone
みんな
co-receptor
共受容体
it is
それはです
and
と
it is two
それは2つです
it can
できる
can infect it
感染する可能性があります
So the problem that often breaks now is to say
したがって、現在よく壊れる問題は次のとおりです
In the countryside
田舎で
In the country you raise pigs
あなたが豚を飼っている国では
Do you know how to raise chickens?
鶏の育て方を知っていますか？
Do you know how to raise ducks?
アヒルの育て方を知っていますか？
so what
だから何
Then when the network rate is over, it will all be mixed together.
その後、ネットワーク速度が終了すると、すべてが混合されます。
So this is a comparison
それでこれは比較です
big problem
大問題
Therefore, when the network rate is completed, it is necessary to command
したがって、ネットワークレートが完了したら、次のコマンドを実行する必要があります。
in the end is
結局のところは
human head
人間の頭
So it's going to be bad fuck right here
だからここではひどいことになるだろう
that's here
それはここです
You can see this virus
このウイルスを見ることができます
The surface of this virus has two very important methods
このウイルスの表面には 2 つの非常に重要な方法があります
One called Hemorrhidim
痔と呼ばれるもの
not right
正しくない
Everyone, just remember the first word
皆さん、最初の単語だけ覚えてください
is H
Hは
The other one is Memidis
もう一人はメミディス
is what we call the hydrolase of the so-called stripping acid
いわゆるストリッピング酸の加水分解酵素と呼ばれるものです
Didn't we just talk about stripping acid?
酸の除去について話したばかりではありませんか?
This specialized hydrolyzed stripping acid
この特殊な加水分解剥離酸
Don't carry them too much
あまり持ち運ばないでください
Just don't recite N
Nを唱えないでください
So often a flu virus
インフルエンザウイルスがよくある
Influenza A virus infection
インフルエンザAウイルス感染症
The doctor has been talking about how much H is
医者はHの量について話しています
how much N
Nはいくらですか
The same one
同じもの
The most recent one is H7N9
最新のものはH7N9です
That changes every year
それは毎年変わります
Vaccinations are usually done every year
予防接種は通常毎年行われます
Please guess for a year
1年くらい当ててみてください
How likely are you to guess correctly?
正しく推測できる可能性はどのくらいですか?
some are ok
一部は大丈夫です
Some can't guess
推測できない人もいる
Then sometimes it is because the map will be worn
それから時々それは地図が摩耗するからです
But you guys are saying this is
でも君たちはこう言ってる
how to say it
それをどのように置くか
I think it has a pretty big effect.
かなり大きな効果があると思います。
can do a defense
防御ができる
Then this Pingnan Wutian Forest
それからこの屏南五田林
Can have 16 kinds
16種類も可能
Then to the last two years
そしてここ2年ほど
only to discover the 17th
17番目を発見するだけ
from that Australian bat
あのオーストラリアンバットから
Australian bat
オーストラリアのコウモリ
The 17th species found in that bat
そのコウモリから17番目に発見された種
Then your map has 9 types
すると、マップには 9 つのタイプがあります
that here
それがここにある
Listen a little bit to say that this virus
このウイルスの言うことを少し聞いてください
it
それ
It will use this H on its surface
この H を表面に使用します
this protein
このタンパク質
with the sugar on the surface of our cells
私たちの細胞の表面にある糖で
to act
行動する
There will be a four other action on its side
その横に他の 4 つのアクションがあります
and then after that it will do
そしてその後はそうなります
Pendococcus
ペンドコッカス
then enters the cell
それからセルに入ります
then copy after
その後コピーしてください
After copying, it will finally go out, right?
コピーしたらいよいよ出ますね。
when it will go out
いつ出ますか
Everyone, it's the surface
皆さん、表面ですよ
We just talked about the surface of our cells
私たちは細胞の表面について話しました。
it has that shoulder
その肩がある
will use it
それを使います
So after the virus replicates and infects
つまり、ウイルスが複製して感染した後、
When he wants to walk out of history
彼が歴史から抜け出したいとき
He can't go out in history
彼は歴史に名を残すことはできない
he's going to do another move
彼は別の動きをするつもりだ
what action
どのような行動
It is to use the N we just talked about
それは、先ほど話した N を使用することです
that half white
その半分は白い
Put the penetrating doctor on the surface of this cell
この細胞の表面に貫通博士を置きます
cut off
切り落とす
he will be released
彼は解放されるでしょう
So now the source of many drugs
現在、多くの麻薬の供給源となっている
passenger flu
乗客のインフルエンザ
these drugs
これらの薬
It's all about the N
すべてはNについてです
the enzyme dedevelopment inhibitor
酵素機能不全阻害剤
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
That is to say, let you suppress N
つまり、Nを抑制しましょう
is to make it non-hydrolyzable
加水分解しないようにすることです
then let this virus
それならこのウイルスを放っておいてください
can stick to the surface of the cell
細胞の表面にくっつく可能性がある
keep it out
それを保ちます
Can't let it out
出せない
further our giant cell
さらに私たちの巨大細胞
will come and cut it off
来て切り捨てるだろう
so right here
だからここで
So this guest flu
それで、このゲストのインフルエンザ
actually show you
実際に見せてもらう
what we just said
私たちが今言ったこと
What is the lean body on the surface of this cell
この細胞の表面にある痩せた体は何ですか
That is to say, today is again
つまり今日もまた
this kind of love
この種の愛
It is the link of the toy acid to the galactose which is Alpha 23
それはアルファ23であるガラクトースへのおもちゃの酸の結合です。
So where do you pay special attention
では、どこに特別な注意を払っていますか
is this place
ここはここですか
It's Alpha 23 to link
リンクするのは Alpha 23 です
what if it's a human
それが人間だったらどうなるか
Man is Alpha 26 to link
男はリンクするアルファ 26 です
So our upper respiratory system
つまり、私たちの上部呼吸器系は
The chromophores on the surface of our cells are this
私たちの細胞の表面にある発色団はこれです
So that is to say
つまり、
pigeon cold
鳩の風邪
you don't come up to talk
あなたは話しに来ない
not contagious
伝染性ではない
Conceptually
理念上
but now
でも今
always these viruses
いつもこのウイルス
it will start to mutate
それは変異を始めるだろう
those mutant viruses
それらの変異ウイルス
It can recognize both the Alpha 23
Alpha 23 の両方を認識できます。
It also recognizes Alpha 26
Alpha 26 も認識します
So when they both recognize Alpha 26
したがって、両者が Alpha 26 を認識すると、
Our bodies experience panic
私たちの体はパニックを起こします
because it's a vibes lawyer
バイブス弁護士だから
one does not know
誰も知らない
Therefore, the human body's supernatural system has always been interested in it from the very beginning.
したがって、人体の超自然的なシステムは、最初から常にそれに興味を持っていました。
There is no way to prevent the epidemic from doing it
流行を防ぐ方法はない
Another long virus
また長いウイルスが
The most frightening thing about the long virus is this type 71
長いウイルスで一番怖いのはこの71型
This is what we call the hand-mouth group
これは私たちが作ったいわゆる手口グループです
What about this? Internet teaching houses will remind children
これについてはどうですか? インターネット教育施設が子供たちに思い出させます
be sure to wash your hands
必ず手を洗ってください
Because this is eaten after dipping your hands in the cake
ケーキに手を浸して食べるので
This virus can pass through the human stomach
このウイルスは人間の胃を通過することができます
will not die very powerful
非常に強力に死ぬことはありません
Because Rui said it was sour
るいが酸っぱいって言ったから
it won't die either
それも死にません
Then go to the intestine and then infect the child's intestine
次に腸に行き、子供の腸に感染します。
After the infection over there, it caused these so-called hand-mouth problems
向こうで感染した後、いわゆる手口の問題が発生しました
that's here
それはここです
on our gut side
私たちの腸側で
Some recent research I found
私が見つけた最近の研究
It should be with #23
#23 にあるはずです
The communities of these links are more related
これらのリンクのコミュニティはより関連性が高くなります
And there's something personal about this official
そして、この役人には個人的なことがあります
or
また
Dungeon fever virus can bubble umbrella or stomach virus
ダンジョンフィーバーウイルスは傘や胃のウイルスを泡立てる可能性があります
Hepatitis, everyone, is umbrella or Dungeness fever
皆さん、肝炎は傘かダンジネス熱です
everyone is clear
誰もが明確です
In the past one or two years, there was no morel disease in the Qingjing Camp
過去1、2年、清京キャンプではアミガサタケ病は発生しなかった
So a lot of those sheep were killed
それでたくさんの羊が殺された
These viruses use heparin on the cell surface
これらのウイルスは細胞表面でヘパリンを使用します
You just mentioned heparin
先ほどヘパリンについて言及しましたね
Heparin on the cell surface is a helper receptor
細胞表面のヘパリンはヘルパー受容体です
to do the infection
感染をする
for example
例えば
This is the scar phlegm reflected by the lights
これは光に反射した瘢痕痰です
Can be used as a host for Amanitavirus
テングタケウイルスの宿主として使用可能
Here we actually have to develop the core instead
ここでは実際にコアを開発する必要があります
Take a test with Master Zhang Yilang
チャン・イーラン先生のテストを受けてください
Let's see that scar phlegm can prevent the infection of this umbrella virus
瘢痕痰がこの傘ウイルスの感染を防ぐことができることを見てみましょう
Next, I want to introduce to you about the candy on the surface of the red snowball.
続いては赤い雪玉の表面のキャンディーについてご紹介したいと思います。
The first thing to mention is the discrimination of the water shape
まず挙げられるのは水の形状の識別です。
Everyone knows that the judgment of water shape is based on our
水の形状の判断は私たちの判断に基づいていることは誰もが知っています。
What is the structure of the sugar that the homework needs to face?
宿題で直面する必要がある砂糖の構造は何ですか？
Hit to identify very hard water
ヒットして超硬水を識別します
The O-shape is the putan sugar that connects sugar to galactose and then to this N-tailed CG
O 字型は、砂糖をガラクトースに接続し、さらにこの N テール CG に接続するプータン糖です。
This is O-shaped
こちらはO字型です
In addition to this fish, Type A also has a galactose with N-tailed CG added
この魚に加えて、A 型には N 尾 CG が付加されたガラクトースもあります。
If it is V-shaped, here is a galactose
V字型ならここはガラクトース
So everyone can see that people with AV shape have both
つまり、AV の体型の人は両方を備えていることが誰にでもわかります。
AV-shaped people have both
AV型の人はその両方を持っています
So the first one will be Hot Blooded
ということで、最初の作品は「熱血」になります
If your parents are both European-type, your child will definitely be European-type
両親がヨーロッパ型なら子供も間違いなくヨーロッパ型になる
If one of your children today is type A or type D
もしあなたのお子さんの中にA型かD型の人がいるとしたら
Some family education came out
家庭教育が少し出てきた
Another very important thing is that you read books, you must not learn from books
もう一つ重要なことは、本を読むことです。本から学んではなりません。
how is this
これはどのように
I have antibodies in my body, and I can accept European-type antibodies
私の体内には抗体があり、ヨーロッパ型の抗体を受け入れることができます
I will recognize him
私は彼を認識します
If it was said that your book was type A or type B that day
あの日、あなたの本がAタイプかBタイプと言われたら
Is there one more here?
ここにもう 1 つありますか?
There is one more thing, can my antibody recognize him? No
もう 1 つありますが、私の抗体は彼を認識できますか? いいえ
so i bother you to take this for what ? foreign matter
それでわざわざこれを何のために持っていくのですか？
i will attack him
私は彼を攻撃します
can't attack him
彼を攻撃することはできない
That day I said you today you are type A
あの日、今日はA型だと言いました
You go to study European style
あなたはヨーロッパスタイルを学びに行きます
Can this thing occupy his position?
こいつが彼の地位を占めることができるだろうか？
so it's ok
だから大丈夫です
Therefore, people of type A or type B can accept the learning of European people.
したがって、A型でもB型でもヨーロッパ人の学びを受け入れることができます。
But type A people cannot accept the learning of European type people.
しかし、A型の人はヨーロッパ型の人たちの学びを受け入れることができません。
Because the two candies are different, right?
だって2つのキャンディーは違うんですよね？
Their sharp noses are unacceptable
彼らの鋭い鼻は受け入れられない
who is the best
誰が一番いい
AV type people
AV型的人
AV-type people are often acceptable
AV タイプの人は受け入れられることが多い
is his advantage
彼の利点は
you tend to go for some chemo
あなたは化学療法を受ける傾向があります
or do some combined treatment
またはいくつかの組み合わせた治療を行う
Blood counts often drop to very low
血球数は非常に低い値まで低下することがよくあります
especially red blood cells
特に赤血球
so inside the hospital
それで病院内で
Often an accepted Epo is used
多くの場合、承認された Epo が使用されます
Epo is a sugar pound white
Epoはシュガーパウンドホワイトです
its a sugar pound white
それはシュガーパウンドホワイトです
Everyone see it
みんな見てね
This is NGIGON
ンギゴンです
There's another OGIGON over here
ここにもオギゴンがいる
Currently this Sugar Pound White
現在このシュガーパウンドホワイト
know something
何かを知っています
For the past year around the world
この一年間、世界中で
I’m doing this for several popular settings
いくつかの一般的な設定でこれを行っています
Because this year's market is also huge
今年のマーケットも大きいので
Then several contacted scientists
その後、何人かの科学者が連絡を取りました
Now they are synthesizing this Sugar Pound White
今、このシュガーパウンドホワイトを合成しています。
It is the Epo who once learned
かつて学んだエポです
Because what comes naturally is a mixture
自然に生まれるものは混合物だから
everyone has been wanting
誰もがそうしたい
synthesize this pure thing
この純粋なものを合成する
relatively controllable
比較的制御可能
Then this is a very popular molecule
これは非常に人気のある分子です
The red snowball finished speaking
赤い雪だるまは話し終えた
Let me tell you about Snowball
スノーボールについて教えてください
The white snowball is the initial step to our origin
白い雪だるまは原点への第一歩
have a great relationship
～とたくさんの関係がある
where is here
ここはどこですか
That is to say, today our snowball
つまり、今日は私たちの雪だるま式です
White snowballs in our veins
私たちの血管には白い雪玉ができている
it's free
それは無料です
it's free scrolling right
右にスクロールすると無料です
then talk about it today
それなら今日それについて話してください
we have a place to shoot
私たちには撮影できる場所があります
Then this shot will stimulate
そうすると、このショットは刺激になります
will release this sieve
このふるいを解放します
Then it will let this blood vessel
そうすれば、この血管は
layer of cells
細胞の層
will express this so-called
いわゆるこれを表現します
Our so-called Eselecting
私たちのいわゆるEセレクション
Then this Eselecting
次に、これを選択すると、
I don't like how to divide
分け方が気に入らない
It will be the same as the one on the white snowball
白い雪だるまと同じになります
This Green Formula X with Cracking Acid
クラッキング酸を配合したグリーンフォーミュラX
this sugar works
この砂糖は効く
after that effect
その効果の後
will slow down the rolling of this white snowball
この白い雪玉の転がりを遅くするだろう
because it rolls freely
自由に転がるので
Then there is interaction here, let it slow down
ここでインタラクションが発生します。速度を落としましょう
Slow down to what? Keep it from rolling
何をするために減速しますか? 回転しないようにします
After not rolling, the white shoe ball can move from this
転がらなくなった後、白い靴のボールはここから移動できます
gap between the cells of the blood vessel wall
血管壁の細胞間の隙間
can pass through
通り抜けることができる
and get to this hurting place
そしてこの痛い場所にたどり着く
Everyone, come here with white shoes
みなさん、白い靴で来てください
it is the enemy also kill
殺すのも敵だ
Your normal cells are also killed
正常な細胞も死滅します
it doesn't recognize
認識しない
It is the killing of soldiers
兵士の殺害です
so it creates inflammation in your tissue
組織内に炎症を引き起こすため、
So the problem is here
問題はここにあります
So this is a more professional
これはより専門的なものです
Just take a look, everyone
ちょっと見てください、皆さん
That is to say this is
つまりこれは
The so-called very stripping acid
いわゆる非常にストリッピングな酸
BV4X
BV4X
this four halls
この4つのホール
Then follow the function of selecting
次に、選択機能に従います
Then this is just a show
それならこれはただのショーだよ
What is the most important thing?
最も重要なことは何ですか?
How do you know if you have inflammation in your body?
体内に炎症があるかどうかはどうやってわかりますか?
The most important thing that doctors usually tell you to go
医者がよく行くように言う最も重要なこと
Did you draw blood?
採血しましたか？
Going to measure the amount of your white snowball
あなたの白い雪玉の量を測りに行きます
what is the main thing
主なものは何ですか
It's our White Snowball's tactic
それは私たちの白い雪だるまの戦術です
win with more
もっと多くで勝つ
so when you have an inflamed place
炎症を起こしている箇所がある場合
it produces a lot
それはたくさん生産します
before being able to come
来られる前に
then deal with it
それからそれに対処する
So when you draw blood and test
それで、採血して検査すると、
Your white snowballs are relatively high
あなたの白い雪玉は比較的高いです
The doctor will tell you that your inflammation
医師はあなたの炎症をこう言います
Is it this way
こうですか
This is seen in this way
これはこんな風に見られます
what happens to your doctor with inflammation
炎症があると医師はどうなりますか
give you antibiotics
抗生物質を与えてください
will let you kill the bacteria
細菌を殺せるようになります
But everyone, if you kill the bacteria today
でも皆さん、今日菌を死滅させたら
If it belongs to this
これに属するものであれば
this kind
この種
Gram-negative of this
これのグラム陰性
Bacteria
細菌
Ladies and gentlemen, if you have a body with a lot
皆さん、たくさんの身体をお持ちの方は
Bacteria have to protect themselves too
細菌も自分自身を守らなければなりません
So it's good for you to resist the crispness
だから、パリパリ感に抵抗するのは良いことです
Are the bacteria dead?
細菌は死んだのでしょうか？
right
右
So when it dies it will release
だから死んだら解放される
It's a cell currency thing, right?
それは携帯通貨の問題ですよね？
The most important one of the plaques of the cell currency is this
携帯通貨のプラークの中で最も重要なものはこれです
We call the so-called Lipid A
いわゆるリピドAと呼ばれるものです
Limb A
手足A
This thing is poisonous
こいつは毒だ
very poisonous
非常に有毒な
so some people say
だから言う人もいる
Some people ask what causes scurvy
壊血病の原因は何かと尋ねる人もいます
That's where Yuanzong comes from
元宗の出身地はそこだ
so you see diabetics
それで糖尿病患者が見えます
How did you die in the end?
結局どうやって死んだの？
it's all because
それはすべてからだ
Because Mosha's nerve circulation is bad
モシャの神経循環が悪いから
then black it out
それから黒く塗りつぶす
Then fattening
それから太る
Then there's the bacterial infection
次に細菌感染です
Bacterial infection ends up with acute sepsis
細菌感染は急性敗血症を引き起こす
Nine and a half out of ten
10中9.5
so it's really
だから本当にそうです
this is torture
これは拷問だ
so you're talking
それであなたは話しているのです
this chronic disease
この慢性疾患
Diabetes is the worst kind
糖尿病は最悪の種類です
because its whole process is like this
なぜなら、そのプロセス全体は次のようなものだからです
That heart attack is the fastest
心臓発作が一番早い
No, just leave, just leave
いや、ただ去ってください、ただ去ってください
That high blood pressure is usually treated
高血圧は通常治療される
companies should know
企業は知っておくべき
Mostly okay
ほとんど大丈夫
So be careful with diabetes
だから糖尿病には気をつけてね
In addition, there are some who are born with us
また、私たちと一緒に生まれてきた人もいます。
The one that has a lot to do here is
ここでやるべきことがたくさんあるのは、
Sperm and primordial union
精子と原始結合
This place also has this identification cleared to this sugar
この場所もこの砂糖にこの識別がクリアされています
mainly here
主にここで
This is a mother's eye
これは母親の目です
There are some membranes on the surface
表面に膜がいくつかあります
A special area we call ZP
ZPと呼ばれる特別な領域
this area
この地域
This region contains some proteins
この領域にはいくつかのタンパク質が含まれています
what about the protein
プロテインはどうですか
It will recognize the sugar on the surface of the sperm
精子の表面の糖分を認識します
identify sugar
識別糖
Then its sperm can stick to it
そうすれば、その精子はそれに付着することができます
after sticking
貼り付けた後
Wait until the sperm enters and combines with sugar
精子が入って糖と結合するまで待ちます
It's like combining with this dye
この染料と組み合わせたような感じです
it emits some grainy stuff
粒子の粗いものを放出します
will become the protection of the community
コミュニティを守ることになる
no more sperm
もう精子はありません
Just don't allow this other sperm to come in again
この他の精子が再び入ってくることを許可しないでください
So this is a process for the whole community
これはコミュニティ全体のプロセスです
so here
それでここで
There will be a very important role in the identification of this sugar
この糖の同定には非常に重要な役割があるだろう
and some are
そしていくつかは
I just found out about this polar region
この極地について最近知りました
It is the fishes of Benshi and Antarctica
弁士と南極の魚たちです
these things
これらの事
Is it cold over there, everyone?
皆さん、あそこは寒いですか？
not like us
私たちとは違う
Our Australia is in the thirties
私たちのオーストラリアは30年代に入っています
So this tree can be done at more than 30 degrees
つまり、この木は30度以上でも大丈夫です
But what if the temperature is as cold as that
しかし、気温がこれほど寒かったらどうなるでしょうか
So these fish are also very powerful
この魚も非常に強力です
it developed the so-called
それはいわゆる
Anti-Dynamic Eggs
アンチダイナミックエッグ
What about these anti-glycan eggs?
これらの抗グリカン卵はどうでしょうか？
it can protect them
それは彼らを守ることができる
keep it still
そのままにしておく
so it's that
だからそれは
Down the tree can also be effective
ダウン・ザ・ツリーも効果的です
then next
それから次へ
Now let me introduce
では紹介しましょう
about this
これについて
Useful plate-based anti-cancer
有用なプレートベースの抗がん剤
or a vaccine against infectious agonists
または感染性アゴニストに対するワクチン
Just now the vice president mentioned at the beginning
今、冒頭で副大統領が申し上げました。
That is, generally speaking, vaccines are used against those who seem to be infected
つまり、一般的にワクチンは、感染していると思われる人に対して使用されます。
How can it be used to fight cancer now?
それを今、がんと闘うためにどのように利用できるでしょうか？
even say there are other
他にもあるとさえ言う
this new disease
この新しい病気
So today’s relationship at this time is going to give three simple examples.
そこで、今日の現時点での関係について、簡単な例を 3 つ挙げます。
Come for your reference
参考までにどうぞ
The first one is milk film and vaccine
第一弾はミルクフィルムとワクチン
This is currently approved by the FDA
これは現在FDAによって承認されています
here in north america
ここ北アメリカで
what is it for
それはなんのためですか
Is it possible to use the so-called Tupanic acid we just talked about?
先ほど話したいわゆるツパニック酸を使用することは可能でしょうか？
It uses this macrotonic acid
このマクロトン酸を使用します
the vaccine
ワクチン
This one is used against this
これはこれに対して使用されます
Milk film and vaccine
ミルクフィルムとワクチン
So you can see that
それでわかります
Normal milk film looks like this
通常のミルクフィルムはこんな感じ
Then when it becomes inflamed
それで炎症が起きると
this place is going to get serious
この場所は大変なことになるだろう
Then this is the tonic acid that can be used
そこで使える強壮酸はこれです
What Fenggang mentioned just now is the so-called anti-cancer vaccine
フォンガン氏が今言及したのは、いわゆる抗がんワクチンです。
Anticancer vaccines are like this
抗がんワクチンはこんな感じ
the first is
一つ目は
It belongs to this kind of WC
このようなトイレに属します
That and the Philippines
それとフィリピン
these so-called
これらのいわゆる
cancerous
癌性の
anticancer
抗癌
This is a lot of these sugars on the surface of R cells
これはR細胞の表面にあるたくさんの糖です
and some are very special
そしていくつかは非常に特別です
Only cells directly above a certain I
特定の I の真上にあるセルのみ
for these antigens to exist
これらの抗原が存在するためには
The most famous one is Robo H
一番有名なのはロボHですね
Robo H is a sugar qualification belonging to Robocerease
ロボHはロボセレーズに所属する砂糖資格です
And this one is about fighting breast cancer
そしてこれは乳がんとの闘いについてです
Then this Robo H is 6 sugar
じゃあこのロボHは6糖です
Then this side is called Linus Serumis
ではこちら側はライナス・セルミスと呼ばれます
is a Lipetrin
リペトリンです
but here they are now
しかし彼らは今ここにいる
Because this is on the surface of the I cell
これはI細胞の表面にあるので、
unique to the surface of primary I cells
主I細胞表面所特有
So I want to say that there is something special about
だから私は何か特別なことがあると言いたいのです
remove this place
この場所を削除します
Then this place goes to connect a
それからこの場所は、
a so-called carrier protein
いわゆるキャリアタンパク質
Then use a carrier protein like this
次に、このようなキャリアタンパク質を使用します
After connecting this sugar with 6 sugars
この糖と6つの糖をつなげると
it can go to induce its that
それを誘発することができます
body antibodies that can then come to recognize it
体内の抗体がそれを認識するようになる
Recognizing it can indicate that you have cells other than
それを特定すると、以外の細胞があることが示される可能性があります。
Its antibody will specifically fight against this
その抗体はこれに対して特異的に対抗します
Currently, this is in the third phase of clinical trials in Taiwan.
現在、台湾で第 3 段階の臨床試験が行われています。
Now do the third period
さあ、3期目をやってみよう
We're going to see if we can succeed
成功できるかどうか見てみるよ
In addition to this, there is another type of Ganglion series we call
これに加えて、ガングリオンシリーズと呼ばれる別のタイプがあります。
This category belongs to the second category, and also belongs to this
このカテゴリは 2 番目のカテゴリに属し、このカテゴリにも属します
bladder related
膀胱関連
There is another one that belongs to the Lactose series
乳糖シリーズにはもう一つあります
So these different bladders
つまり、これらの異なる膀胱
its in different cancer cells
さまざまながん細胞に存在する
It all has different amount of rendering
レンダリング量がすべて異なります
Another one is the so-called anti-inner ridge
もう一つは、いわゆる反インナーリッジです。
Development of vaccine against spinal cord
脊髄に対するワクチンの開発
At present, many of these groups are studying
現在、これらのグループの多くは研究を行っています。
This is mainly for what we call the so-called
これは主に、いわゆる
It's GPRN, it's the staff members of these five churches who have base eyes
それはGPRNです、卑劣な目をしているのはこの5つの教会の職員です
Then go to develop, to fight against this bad deed
それから開発に行って、この悪事と戦うために
That is also currently under development.
こちらも現在開発中です。
It's finally the seventh
ついに7回目です
This one is about Tanghe philosophy
これは丹河哲学についてです
a personal servant
個人的な使用人
Everyone because in this academic research
皆さん、この学術研究では
Often we just sometimes run into the fact that we have geometric layers
幾何学的なレイヤーがあるという事実に時々遭遇することがあります。
When Teacher Liao Juncheng taught us before
以前廖俊成先生が私たちに教えてくれたとき
The first one, the first thing I thought of was carbon six four
最初のもの、最初に思いついたのはカーボンシックスフォーでした
This is because the speaker in Germany is a football player
ドイツの講演者はサッカー選手だからだ
So this is a thoughtful molecule, everyone knows
これは思慮深い分子です、誰もが知っています
I didn't just talk about the structure of a hall
ホールの構造だけを話したわけではない
Is this the expression
これがその表現なのか
Then we have a plan
それから計画があります
There is a class of artistic molecules that is your link pill
リンクの丸薬となる芸術的な分子のクラスがあります
How do you connect it with another link pill with a carbon carbon piece with a big V?
大きなVの付いたカーボンピースを備えた別のリンクピルとどうやって接続するのでしょうか？
If you can connect, then this is an artist
繋がればこの人はアーティスト
Yes or no
はい、もしくは、いいえ
Look out, friends
気をつけてね、友達
This kind of artist so far only has this
この手のアーティストは今のところこれしかない
Quads of this we're after QBEN
これの 4 つを私たちは QBEN を追っています
This one was made by a synthetic chemist
これは合成化学者が作ったものです
This is done by a professor from the National Education University
これは国立教育大学の教授によって行われます。
the best
最高の
other these
その他これら
3 sides, 5 sides, 6 sides, 7 sides, a little bit of this can't be done
3面、5面、6面、7面、これはちょっと無理
so far
ここのところ
Then this is a big challenge for us to synthesize
それでは、これを合成するのは私たちにとって大きな課題です
Then I feel very inaccurate
それから私は非常に不正確に感じます
But I'm thinking that my genetics can't change
でも遺伝子は変えられないと思っている
can i use another way
別の方法を使用できますか
Then you see
そうすればわかります
We all figured out how to make this carton paper
みんなでこのカートン紙の作り方を考えました
See if we can make hexagons because of this need
このおかげで、必要に応じて六角形を作成できるかどうかを確認してください
Our height can vary
私たちの身長はさまざまです
Then the pattern above can be changed
その後、上記のパターンを変更できます
then here everyone
それでは皆さんここに
my personal feeling
私の個人的な感情
we do bomb science
私たちは爆弾の科学を行っています
it's sweeter
就比較sweet
then origami is fun
それなら折り紙は楽しいですよ
Origami is like doing research
折り紙は研究に似ています
each different shape
それぞれ違う形
The length of its side is related to this
辺の長さがこれに関係します
Still need some math to understand
理解するにはまだ数学が必要です
So three sides, four sides, five sides
つまり、三面、四面、五面
Different polygons have different relationships
異なるポリゴンには異なる関係があります
Then this is a triangle relationship
そうすると三角関係ですね
that's ok
それで大丈夫です
A piece of paper can fold a fit
一枚の紙でぴったりと折りたたむことができます
Another piece of paper can cover a box lid
別の紙で箱の蓋を覆うことができます
we can shade various polygons
さまざまなポリゴンにシェーディングを適用できます
Everyone, this kindness
みなさん、この優しさ
I also spent ten years
私も10年かかりました
just got it out
ちょうどそれを取り出した
Now you can do all kinds of different polygons
あらゆる種類の異なるポリゴンを作成できるようになりました
in theory
理論上
Can also do 7, 8, 9, 10
7、8、9、10もできます
Samples I can bring today
本日お持ちいただけるサンプル
that is
あれは
this is carton paper
これはカートン紙です
means you can open
開けることができることを意味します
a box body
ボックス本体
The other is the lid
もう一つは蓋です
Then there can be different polygons
そうすれば、さまざまなポリゴンが存在する可能性があります
I brought three today
今日は3つ持ってきました
Two to three, our vice president
二対三、私たちの副社長
668 orders
668順
Thanks
ありがとう
Another one I'm of course leaving me with a question
もう一つ、もちろん質問があります
I want to ask everyone
みんなに聞きたい
Give him the right answer
彼に正しい答えを与えてください
so when there is a problem
それで問題があったとき
so this is
それでこれは
I personally think that this is a
個人的にはこれだと思います
to the elderly
高齢者へ
You can watch your Mosha nerves
モシャ神経を監視できます
This change above is something you can think about every day
上記の変化は毎日考えられることです
So I think the problem that the old people have now
だから私は今、老人が食べることが問題だと思う
more and more
だんだん
this is a pretty good one
これはかなり良いものです
so everyone
だからみんな
What you see here are a few simple
ここに表示されているものはいくつかの簡単なものです
you know i have done all kinds of different
私があらゆる種類の異なることをしてきたことを知っていますか
I have printed it out
プリントアウトしました
There are some
幾つかある
You are also interested
あなたも興味があります
you are interested to see
見ることに興味がありますか
I've been wanting to say
ずっと言いたかったんだ
Publisher of our hospital
当院の発行者
It's all about literature
それはすべて文学に関するものです
can you say this
これを言えますか
i never knew
私は知らなかった
because i do science
私は科学をやっているので
I never dared to ask
あえて尋ねることはなかった
Because I'm afraid of being talked about by the hospital, it's not as good as a job
病院の悪口を言われるのが怖くて仕事にならない
I want to say am I
言いたいのは私ですか
You can use Saturday and Sunday
土曜・日曜もご利用いただけます
want to say half water
半分水と言いたい
so those outside
だから外にいる人たちは
Amount that can sell this paper
この紙が売れる金額
But it seems that it is not bad to ask for a piece
でも一枚頼むのも悪くないようです
yes, this is
はい、これは
I'll see how it works as soon as I talk
話したらすぐにそれがどのように機能するかがわかります
A book that can be covered first
最初に取り上げられる本
this is my current wish
これが私の今の願いです
but because it has been
しかし、そうであったため
It's ugly like I took it
私が撮ったように醜いです
If you look at the picture they took
彼らが撮った写真を見てみると
you can take beautiful pictures
美しい写真を撮ることができます
that this is a person
これが人だということ
a purely personal interest
純粋に個人的な興味
so i conclude
だから私は結論を出します
what we are talking about today
今日私たちが話していること
seven themes
7つのテーマ
and then
その後
From the general introduction to the final
概要紹介から最後まで
This masking aspect
このマスキングの側面
that this
これは
I finally want to thank you
最後に感謝したいと思います
listen very patiently
とても辛抱強く聞いてください
Because it's really a cold scene
本当に寒い現場だから
one and a half hours
1時間半
So if there are two slides
したがって、スライドが 2 つある場合、
want to share with you
あなたと共有したい
that one is
それは
Qipenjiao
七本角
this is
これは
Our Ziyi State Security Officer in Taiwan
台湾のZiyi国家保安官
thank you very much
どうもありがとうございます
We walked in the courtyard of the old courtyard
私たちは古い中庭の中庭を歩きました
Is there an ecological stone opposite the Biochemical Institute?
生化学研究所の向かいに生態石はありますか？
There was a chessboard corner
チェス盤コーナーがありました
checkerboard corner
市松模様のコーナー
Have you seen it?
見たことありますか？
that's really beautiful
それは本当に美しいです
and only open at night
そして夜のみ営業
It's like setting off fireworks when it's on.
花火が上がると花火が上がるようなものです。
So if you guys are going to end up walking over
それで、もし君たちが結局そこを歩いて行くつもりなら
is it blooming now
今咲いてますか？
The other one is more special
もう一つはもっと特別です
is a walker about this technological advancement
この技術の進歩についてよく知る人です
this is my personal feeling
これは私の個人的な感情です
Said a word to me Da Ying Shi Tan
ダ・イン・シー・タンが私に一言言った
He said he was hot on the day that technology will tear down the moon and human interaction
テクノロジーが月と人間の交流を破壊する日には、熱くなったと彼は語った
The world will become the age of idiots
世界はバカの時代になる
Guys, this thing is with us now
皆さん、これはもう私たちと一緒です
already found
すでに見つかりました
Regardless of the construction vehicle
工事車両問わず
regardless of writing luck
筆記運とは関係なく
Even from the MRT, from this line, you have to change to another line
MRTからでもこの路線からは別の路線に乗り換えなければなりません
That person can still look down the stairs and up the stairs like this
あの人は今でもこうして階段の下も階段の上も見られる
I really admire him, he is not afraid to bump into
私は彼を本当に尊敬します、彼はぶつかることを恐れません
Then this has become an eyeful
そうすると、これは目玉になりました
When I formed that, what was it that I was discussing?
それを結成したとき、私は何を話し合っていましたか?
Discuss the so-called Internet idiom certificate
いわゆるインターネットイディオム証明書について議論する
Then it's like taking drugs
それなら麻薬を服用しているようなものだ
to that music venue
あの音楽会場へ
can borrow
借りることができます
I've connected like this
こんな感じで繋ぎました
So like we shared doing a lot of the same period of popular school avoidance
同じ時期に流行った学校回避を私たちが共有したように
will happen in the next five to ten years
今後5年から10年以内に起こるだろう
In the past two years, I heard that the ophthalmologist's life is very good.
この２年間、眼科医の生活はとても良いと聞きました。
The glasses store sells a lot
メガネ屋さんはたくさん売ってます
What is the next one? The next one is avoidance
次は何ですか? 次は回避です
Because that's what children face
それが子どもたちの直面することだから
I'm exaggerating a bit more, I also saw a mother pushing a music
少し大げさですが、母親が音楽を押しているのも見ました
you are asleep
あなたは眠っている
In front of the music there is a
音楽の前には、
He just touched there one by one.
彼はただ一つ一つそこに触れただけだった。
It's in there
そこにあるよ
He slowly took one himself
彼はゆっくりと自分でそれを手に取りました
I see it
分かった
how could he do this
彼はどうしてこんなことができたのか
this is really
ほんとに
i think
私が思うに
if i can't deny
否定できないなら
Is the progress of the computer is really
コンピュータの進歩は本当にあるのか
very important nothing wrong
非常に重要なことは何も間違っていません
but
しかし
nothing is
何もない
hope not to overdo it
無理をしないことを願っています
overused words
使い古された言葉
Actually to the end
実は最後まで
only our own body
私たち自身の体だけ
I want to share this with you
これをあなたと共有したいと思います
thank you all thank you
みんなありがとう、ありがとう
We are very grateful to Professor Hong
ホン教授にとても感謝しています
Red Clear Rescue
レッドクリアレスキュー
great introduction to us
私たちへの素晴らしい紹介
This Tang Dynasty is interesting
この唐の時代は面白いです
He today no matter from the scientific point of view
今日の彼は科学的な観点から見ても問題ありません
From an artistic point of view
芸術的な観点から
Or from the perspective of disease prevention
あるいは病気予防の観点から
from a therapeutic perspective
治療的な観点から
also give us a lot
私たちにもたくさん与えてください
such a valuable knowledge
とても貴重な知識
actually listen to people
実際に人の話を聞く
watch this with you
これを一緒に見てください
iPhone iPad 3.0
iPhone iPad 3.0
that kind of thing is very different
そういうのは全然違うよ
is that we have good human-to-human interaction
それは人間同士の交流が良好であるということです
What about after the appointment?
約束の後はどうですか？
Of course we also hope that everyone and our generals
もちろん、私たちは皆さんと将軍たちがそうしてくれることを望んでいます。
Have better Q&A interaction
より良いQ&Aインタラクションを実現する
I don't know if you have any questions
何か質問があるか分かりませんが
come to ask
尋ねに来てください
Haolai Zhou Yueqing
ハオライ・チョウ・ユエチン
ask the professor
教授に聞く
Thank you so much
非常感謝
it was a very good speech
とても良いスピーチでした
I come every month to listen to something as brilliant as this rarely
私は毎月来て、これほど素晴らしいものを聴くことはめったにありません
Thanks
ありがとう
ask the professor
教授に聞く
my question is simple
私の質問は簡単です
and you please don't scare me
そして私を怖がらせないでください
but i want to know
でも知りたいです
The professor just mentioned dried inulin
先ほど教授は乾燥イヌリンについて言及しました
That is to say, you eat the leaves and they are very sweet
つまり、葉を食べるととても甘いのです。
non-toxic and harmless
無毒で無害
can we use dried inulin leaves
乾燥したイヌリンの葉を使用できますか
In place of that sugar heaven
あの砂糖天国の代わりに
is now used
現在是用
I think it should be possible now Tianju Tang
今ならできるはずだと思う
In fact, in Japan or in the mainland, they have to extract
実際、日本でも本土でも、彼らは抽出する必要があります。
I am selling this Tianjutang exclusively
私はこの天珠湯を独占的に販売しています
In Taiwan, you actually go online to report what happened in Tianjutang
台湾では、実際にオンラインにアクセスして天柱堂で何が起こったかを報告します
You can also find agents
エージェントも探せます
So you can actually buy
実際に購入できるので、
But that means the Department of Health may not have announced it positively.
しかし、それは保健省が積極的に発表していない可能性があることを意味します。
so that everyone can use more
みんながもっと使えるように
If you go to the flower market to buy leaves to eat
食べる葉っぱを買いに花市場に行ったら
It's okay to be in the south
南国だから大丈夫だよ
In fact, the sweetness is of course not as sweet as it is stored
実際、甘さはもちろん保存されているほど甘くありません
It means that if you eat it, you will feel a sweet taste in your mouth, there is nothing wrong with it
食べると口の中に甘い味がするという意味ですが、問題はありません。
But it's not as sweet as extracted, isn't it?
でも抽出したほど甘くないですよね。
Yes, what is extracted is what is stored
はい、抽出されたものが保存されます
Thank you and the second question
ありがとうございます、そして2番目の質問です
It's the hay that your professor mentioned just now
それは今先生がおっしゃった干し草です
So if hay is good for the body too
まあ、干し草も体に良いならね
Buying hay flakes will make tea and you feel very dry
干し草のフレークを買うとお茶ができて、とても乾燥した気分になる
I am studying medicine myself.
私自身も医学を勉強しています。
Yes, because many people will talk about this balance
はい、多くの人がこのバランスについて話すでしょうから
So I still suggest that you can ask a Chinese doctor to see
したがって、中国の医師に診てもらうことをお勧めします。
Because it depends on your physique whether it is suitable for this kind of thing
こういうのに合うかどうかは体格にもよるので
Because some people have different constitutions, some are hot and some are cold.
人によって体質が違うので、暑い人、寒い人がいます。
Thank you Jiaqi
ありがとうジアチー
ok who else
わかりました、他に誰がいますか
come welcome sir please
いらっしゃいませ、どうぞよろしくお願いします
sorry for the viewers
視聴者さんごめんなさい
Then I think that several years ago we read in a newspaper in Taiwan that
それから数年前、台湾の新聞で次のようなことを読んだと思います。
the british said to the newspaper
イギリス人は新聞にこう言った
There is a universal vaccine for influenza A
インフルエンザAには万能ワクチンがある
But when I saw that news about three or four years ago, there was no follow-up
しかし、私がそのニュースを3、4年前に見たときは、その後の続報はありませんでした。
Then I think a question is to say
それから、質問はこう言うことだと思います
All of the influenza A does it have some missing pieces
すべてのインフルエンザ A にはいくつかの欠落部分がありますか?
It is an invariant and has antigenic properties
それは不変であり、抗原特性を持っています
Then I don’t know you just mentioned that there are so many H and H and there are so many N
それから、H と H が非常に多く、N が非常に多いと先ほどおっしゃったのはわかりません。
and so much more
などなど
Every now and then a new type A flu
時々新型A型インフルエンザが流行る
We're scared to death
私たちは死ぬほど怖いです
even water
水さえも
It is possible that in the section of new material research
新素材研究の分野では可能性があります。
Find books from the structure of carbohydrates
糖の構造から本を探す
Type A parts can
タイプAパーツは
It can be said to be a marker for the basis of my vaccine development
私のワクチン開発の基礎の目印とも言えます
If so, will something like this be developed in the future?
もしそうなら、将来的にはこのようなものが開発されるのでしょうか？
Don't be afraid of newcomers coming out
新人が出てくることを恐れないでください
It's ok to call first
まずはお電話からでも大丈夫です
so that's my idea thanks
それが私のアイデアです、ありがとう
Thank you
ありがとう
Because it's everyone's dream
それはみんなの夢だから
I hope you can find the so-called
いわゆるものを見つけていただければ幸いです
broad-spectrum vaccine
広域ワクチン
can beat everything
すべてに勝つことができる
words here
ここの言葉
Most of the previous research and development was aimed at
これまでの研究開発のほとんどは、
You just talked about a half-blank paper here
あなたは今ここで半分白紙の紙について話しました
So are you able to find
それで、あなたは見つけることができますか
a common sequence
共通的一個 sequence
you target that sequence
そのシーケンスをターゲットにします
is the development antibody
開発抗体です
make a vaccine
ワクチンを作る
This is the way it used to be
これがかつてのやり方です
Use this type to find
このタイプを使用して検索します
but that means
しかしそれは意味します
Can cohabitation be found?
同棲は見つかるのか？
Can do a better sequence
より良いシーケンスを実行できる
this is a problem
これは問題だ
Our dean is doing it
私たちの学部長がやってます
Our dean and horse test
学部長と馬のテスト
one of the things they do is say
彼らがすることの一つはこう言うことです
This Timaru Dilim
このティマル・ディリム
He actually has a lot of these on the surface
実際、彼は表面上にこれらのことをたくさん持っています
N-Guy icon
Nガイのアイコン
They found that light
彼らはその光を見つけた
If you come out like this
こうやって出てきたら
Go to indus N-Guy body
indus N-Guy の本体に移動します
Because those N-Guy icons are big
N-Guyのアイコンが大きいから
or cover up
あるいは隠蔽する
will cover him
彼をカバーします
So that N-Guy body's
N-Guy の体は
It's definitely not that good of a choice.
確かにそれはあまり良い選択ではありません。
the hydrolyzed protein
加水分解されたタンパク質
Those N-Guy icons cut off
N-Guy のアイコンが切り取られました
Cut off leaving only one sugar
砂糖を1つだけ残して切ります
is the first candy
初めてのお菓子です
It's NGuy CO-Gay Glucosamine
NGuy CO-ゲイ グルコサミンです
The sugar is still on the egg white
卵白には砂糖がまだ残っています
They found that this is how
彼らは、これがその方法であることを発見しました
Glycoprotein
糖タンパク質
then that
それからそれ
when antibodies come
抗体が来たら
it can
できる
identifiable
識別可能な
Many antibodies recognize egg vesicles
多くの抗体が卵胞を認識する
Such a glycoprotein
このような糖タンパク質は
Today it doesn't matter how much H you are
今日はどれだけHしても関係ない
Many and few of those sugar egg lilies
砂糖卵ユリの多くと少数
Because Englekensla watch those many different
イングルケンスラはそれらの多くの異なるものを見ているからです
But you cut off the exterior
でもあなたは外側を切り取った
As long as the most basic sugar in it
最も基本的な砂糖が入っている限り
that's all the same
それはすべて同じです
So they are developing now, that is to say
つまり、彼らは現在開発中です、つまり
Can this thing be made universal?
これを普遍化できるでしょうか？
Universal's Vaccine
ユニバーサルのワクチン
This is what our dean is currently doing with that teacher Ma Fang.
これが私たちの学部長が馬芳先生と現在行っていることです。
Well, of course everyone knows this.
もちろんこれは誰でも知っています
You come out with a sexual concept of any thing
あなたは何でも性的な概念をカミングアウトします
Then after many visual tests
その後、多くの視覚テストを行った後、
I don't know if they have already transferred the record to the company
彼らがすでに記録を会社に転送したかどうかはわかりません
But that is to say, has it entered clinical trials?
しかし、それは臨床試験に入ったのだろうか？
Might have to wait for further news
さらなるニュースを待つ必要があるかもしれない
After all, we hope that our dean will not be told by him
結局のところ、私たちの学部長が彼から言われないことを願っています
right
右
This is mainly
これは主に
This is mainly to say that it really didn't work out.
これは主に、本当にうまくいかなかったことを言いたいのです。
Definitely not mentioned by him
確かに彼は言及していない
I can tell you like this
こんな風に言えるよ
But this thing just takes time
でも、これって時間がかかるだけなんです
we're going to push
私たちは押していきます
good
良い
come to a mirror
鏡の前に来てください
May I ask why the cranberry has no effect after adding Liposong?
なぜクランベリーがLiposongを加えた後に効果がないのか聞いてもいいですか？
I found it on two roads, but I don't know how, it is the benchmark of its function
2 つの道路で見つけましたが、どうやって見つけたのかわかりません。これはその機能のベンチマークです
Because of course it is possible to bring this little Ami's comparative comfort
もちろんこの小さな亜美の比較的快適さをもたらすことができるので
So it can be packaged by Liposong, so it can be brought in
Liposongで梱包できるので持ち込み可能です
In Taiwan, I know a company that is doing Weiss, and now the stock has been rising recently
台湾でワイスをやっている会社を知っていますが、最近株価が上がってきています。
Because it is the part of the application that seems to be pretty good
それはアプリケーションの中で非常に優れていると思われる部分だからです
But I don't know the real function benchmark, sorry
しかし、実際の機能のベンチマークはわかりません、申し訳ありません
Don't forget I just had a question for you guys
皆さんに質問があるのを忘れないでください
If you have any questions, we will ask Teacher Hong to ask questions
ご質問がございましたら、ホン先生に質問させていただきます
He will give you this beautiful elbow
彼はあなたにこの美しい肘を与えてくれるでしょう
May I
いいですか
still have a question
まだ質問があります
i'm not a problem
私は問題ないよ
I also want to add to what I just said about Liposong
Liposong について今述べたことに付け加えたいと思います。
Because someone who supplements Liposong will receive cancer cell
リポソンを補う人はガン細胞を受け取ることになるため
Less likely to receive normal cell
正常な細胞を受け取る可能性が低い
Because many neuroparticles have this characteristic
多くの神経粒子がこの特性を持っているため
Then if he does not receive normal cells
その後、正常な細胞を受け取らなかった場合
It will have fewer side effects
副作用も少なくなりますよ
Thank you for our director's supplement
院長の補足ありがとうございます
this is a very important thing
これはとても重要なことです
Come on, demonstrate a problem
さあ、問題を示してください
I'm curious
私は興味がある
Talking about the C2 acid of poisonous starch
有毒デンプンのC2酸についての話
followed by back dripping C2 acid
続いてC2酸を逆滴下する
Why add this dropwise C2 acid
なぜこの C2 酸を滴下するのか
what chemical reaction
何の化学反応
Let it taste more Q
もっと味わってください Q
what structure is causing this feeling
どのような構造がこの感情を引き起こしているのか
I didn't discuss this
これについては議論しませんでした
I will ask the master who made this starch
このでんぷんを作った師匠に聞いてみます
Professor Wang
王教授
He has to apply for a patent
彼は特許を申請しなければならない
then later failed
その後失敗しました
These are the best
これらが最高です
if pass everywhere
どこにでも通れば
This is terrible
これはひどい
the reason behind this
この背後にある理由
I didn't show up first
最初に現れなかった
yes
はい
ask a question
質問する
even if it makes sense
たとえそれが理にかなっていても
how bad
どんなに悪い
I seem to see it now
今見えてる気がする
Eating naked eyes is like being completely dead
裸眼で食べると完全に死んだようなもの
Some so-called over-standard
いわゆる規格外のものもある
But what about passing the bid?
しかし、入札を通過した場合はどうなるでしょうか?
Are you going to do good?
うまくやるつもりですか？
this is
これは
Of course, there is an announcement from the Department of Health
もちろん厚生労働省からの発表もある
That is how much weight per day
それは1日あたりの体重です
probably can say
おそらく言えるでしょう
how much is that
いくらですか
But I feel that is the highest standard
でもそれが最高水準だと思う
but everyone
でもみんな
There are always several kinds of food you eat every day
毎日食べるものは常に数種類あります
But so many additions
しかし追加が多すぎて
a lot of these
これらの多くの
This is not the only one
これだけではありません
so here
それでここで
In fact, if you are outside
実際、外にいると
can buy books
本が買える
so-called food additives
いわゆる食品添加物
Have you seen this book
この本を見たことがありますか
there is a japanese
有一個日本人
So inside the job ended up he wrote a book
それで彼は仕事の中で本を書くことになった
is the thing that unmasks these food additives
これらの食品添加物を明らかにするものです
this word is
この言葉は
at present
現在のところ
That is to say, poison experts on the side of Long Roots.
つまり、ロングルーツ側の毒の専門家。
what he did he did with that animal
彼はその動物に対して何をしたのか
He found out that he was not good for his kidneys
彼は腎臓に良くないことが分かりました
It's not good for the kidneys, so he concluded that
それは腎臓に良くないので、彼は次のように結論付けました。
If you take too much of this stuff
こういうものを摂りすぎると
permanent damage to the kidneys
腎臓への永久的な損傷
That's why he proposed that he would do kidney dialysis
だからこそ彼は腎臓透析を提案したのです
But our Sun Yuxuan
しかし、私たちの孫玉軒
Dean's daughter Sun Yuxuan
ディーンの娘、孫玉軒
Professor Sun Yuxuan
孫玉璇教授
He is a professor at the National Taiwan University Laboratory
彼は国立台湾大学研究所の教授です
He brought up another one that he felt
彼は感じたもう一つのことを持ち出した
That is the difference between animals and people
それが動物と人間の違いです
So people's words don't seem to be that serious
だから人々の言葉はそれほど深刻ではないように見える
So he thinks that further research is needed
したがって、彼はさらなる研究が必要だと考えている
Let's see if it's really possible
本当に可能かどうか見てみましょう
right
右
but still
それでも
always more than a word
常に一言以上のもの
I feel like saying
と言いたくなる
many things should not be added
多くのものは追加すべきではありません
should not be added
追加すべきではありません
But the manufacturer is
しかしメーカーは、
want to make money
お金を稼ぎたい
so he'll add these things
それで彼はこれらのことを追加します
But I feel like saying
でも私はそう感じます
our government
私たちの政府
we are sometimes
私たちは時々います
Tai easy compromise
太容易妥協
just by you
あなただけで
in order to compromise
妥協するために
is about to become a
になろうとしています
The so-called allowable range
いわゆる許容範囲
This makes people feel
これは人々に感じさせます
doesn't seem so good
あまり良くないようです
because of that tolerance
その寛容さのせいで
it will sometimes be blurry
時々ぼやけてしまいます
So like social gold
ソーシャルゴールドのようなもの
Originally it was fixed and could not be added
もともと修正されていて追加できませんでした
what's going on now
今何が起こっているのか
How many PPTs are available
利用可能な PPT の数
right
右
Is that mountain giant Qingan there?
山の巨人清安は存在するのか？
Plasticizer
可塑剤
toxic starch
有毒でんぷん
Guess why next
次はその理由を推測してください
Excuse me
すみません
that's for the eyes
それは目のためです
your eyes
あなたの目
It's also easy to pick one by one
1つずつ選ぶのも簡単です
So I think this is really a big problem.
ですから、これは本当に大きな問題だと思います。
ok if there are no other questions
他に質問がなければOK
Let's now invite Professor Huang to ask us questions
それでは黄教授に質問してもらいましょう
ok, simple question
はい、簡単な質問です
Everyone, I just mentioned SARS, right?
皆さん、先ほどSARSについて触れましたね。
SARS outbreak expected in 2003
SARS の流行は 2003 年に予想されている
This year is also a better tenth anniversary
今年もより良い10周年になりますように
Did everyone forget
みんな忘れてたのか
You said who has the government computer?
誰が政府のコンピューターを持っていると言いましたか？
Let's mention this matter
この件について言及しましょう
but you know what
しかし、あなたは何を知っていますか
Back in 2003 we were in front of the TV
2003年に私たちはテレビの前にいました
It was really troublesome at that time
あの時は本当に面倒だった
I don't know how you feel
あなたの気持ちはわかりません
I saw a face at that time
その時の顔が見えた
appear on tv
テレビに出演する
then tell us this stuff
それならこのことを教えてください
How should you prevent
どうやって防げばいいのか
right, you should have a fever
そう、熱があるはずです
It's contagious because he has a fever, right?
熱があるから伝染するんですよね？
You can't go to public places, and you have raised the so-called 2 seconds to enter a public place, is that right?
公共の場所には行けない、いわゆる公共の場所に入るまでの二秒を引き上げたわけですよね。
At that time, Taiwan had the least number of hospital patients, and it was the cleanest time, because everyone wore masks, and it was really the best time
当時、台湾は入院患者が最も少なく、誰もがマスクを着用していたので最も清潔な時期で、本当に最高の時期でした
Do you still remember the vulgar chief? You raised your hand, high school student, do you want to hurry up and put the second
下品な番長をまだ覚えていますか?手を挙げた高校生、急いで二番目を出しますか?
right
右
If at that time someone told me there was no such thing
もしあのとき誰かがそんなことはないって言ったら
and then to solve
そして解決するために
I don't want to die
死にたくない
At that time, the whole has really spread.
そのときは本当に全体が広がってきました。
But let me add
しかし、付け加えさせてください
this person is not important
この人は重要ではありません
the most important thing is each of you
最も重要なのはあなたたち一人一人です
Each of you has two body temperatures
あなた方にはそれぞれ 2 つの体温があります
There are measures to cooperate with the government
政府と連携した施策もある
without the cooperation of the people
国民の協力がなければ
this person has nothing
この人は何も持っていない
but i really thank you
でも本当にありがとう
The teacher also accepts this gift from me very much.
先生も私からのこの贈り物をとても喜んで受け止めてくれました。
Now I don't know how to speak
今はどうやって話せばいいのか分かりません
But we are very grateful
しかし、私たちはとても感謝しています
Professor Hong gave us a wonderful speech
ホン教授が素晴らしいスピーチをしてくれました
Just what you told the classmates who watched us
私たちを見ていたクラスメートにあなたが言ったこと
we have a lot of speeches
私たちはたくさんのスピーチをしています
this is deep for me
これは私にとって深いです
And everyone can understand
そして誰もが理解できる
And then have a good understanding of Don
そしてドンをよく理解する
thanks again
再度、感謝します
Professor Hong's speech to us
ホン教授の講演
Thanks
ありがとう
you
あなた